{
	"description": "熟字訓、当て字一覧 from https://goo.gl/RjuvpH",
	"deck": [{
		"question": "嗚呼",
		"answers": ["ああ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吁嗟",
		"answers": ["ああ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "于嗟",
		"answers": ["ああ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弧光灯",
		"answers": ["あーくとう",
		"あーくらいと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扁桃",
		"answers": ["あーもんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "敵娼",
		"answers": ["あいかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匕首",
		"answers": ["あいくち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "氷菓子",
		"answers": ["あいすくりーむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼奴",
		"answers": ["あいつ",
		"あやつ",
		"かやつ",
		"きゃつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鮎魚女",
		"answers": ["あいなめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鮎並",
		"answers": ["あいなめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生憎",
		"answers": ["あいにく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "媾曳",
		"answers": ["あいびき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "相部屋",
		"answers": ["あいべや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白馬",
		"answers": ["あおうま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梧桐",
		"answers": ["あおぎり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緑啄木鳥",
		"answers": ["あおげら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石蓴",
		"answers": ["あおさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青緡",
		"answers": ["あおざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青繦",
		"answers": ["あおざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒿雀",
		"answers": ["あおじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青鵐",
		"answers": ["あおじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒿雀",
		"answers": ["あおじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青麻",
		"answers": ["あおそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青苧",
		"answers": ["あおそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青底翳",
		"answers": ["あおそこひ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青苔",
		"answers": ["あおのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青海苔",
		"answers": ["あおのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緑苔",
		"answers": ["あおのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青葉木莵",
		"answers": ["あおはずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青葉梟",
		"answers": ["あおはずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緑鳩",
		"answers": ["あおばと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水綿",
		"answers": ["あおみどろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "障泥",
		"answers": ["あおり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "障泥烏賊",
		"answers": ["あおりいか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "満江紅",
		"answers": ["あかうきくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤狗母魚",
		"answers": ["あかえそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "見風乾",
		"answers": ["あかしで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤翡翠",
		"answers": ["あかしょうびん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤麻",
		"answers": ["あかそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤苧",
		"answers": ["あかそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "贖児",
		"answers": ["あがちご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "班田",
		"answers": ["あかちだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幹林院",
		"answers": ["あかでみー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤蜻蛉",
		"answers": ["あかとんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "贓贖司",
		"answers": ["あがないもののつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茜草",
		"answers": ["あかね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地血",
		"answers": ["あかね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明衣",
		"answers": ["あかは",
		"あかはとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柳葉菜",
		"answers": ["あかばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白地",
		"answers": ["あからさま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明白",
		"answers": ["あからさま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "安芸",
		"answers": ["あき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋入梅",
		"answers": ["あきついり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋黴雨",
		"answers": ["あきついり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋茄子",
		"answers": ["あきなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "榔楡",
		"answers": ["あきにれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋日和",
		"answers": ["あきびより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "商人",
		"answers": ["あきんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灰汁",
		"answers": ["あく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灰酒",
		"answers": ["あくざけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緊唇",
		"answers": ["あくち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "欠伸",
		"answers": ["あくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "趺坐",
		"answers": ["あぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡座",
		"answers": ["あぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡坐",
		"answers": ["あぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盤領",
		"answers": ["あげくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳳蝶",
		"answers": ["あげはちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木通",
		"answers": ["あけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木通",
		"answers": ["あけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丁翁",
		"answers": ["あけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山女",
		"answers": ["あけび",
		"やまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "揚げ雲雀",
		"answers": ["あげひばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "総角",
		"answers": ["あげまき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤秀",
		"answers": ["あこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤魚鯛",
		"answers": ["あこうだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牽牛花",
		"answers": ["あさがお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白辛樹",
		"answers": ["あさがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朝餉",
		"answers": ["あさげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朝勤",
		"answers": ["あさじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浅葱",
		"answers": ["あさつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糸葱",
		"answers": ["あさつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明後日",
		"answers": ["あさって"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浅傷",
		"answers": ["あさで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海豹",
		"answers": ["あざらし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水豹",
		"answers": ["あざらし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛤仔",
		"answers": ["あさり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜細亜",
		"answers": ["あじあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海驢",
		"answers": ["あしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葦牙",
		"answers": ["あしかび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八仙花",
		"answers": ["あじさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫陽花",
		"answers": ["あじさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿輸迦王",
		"answers": ["あしょーかおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿育王",
		"answers": ["あしょーかおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明日",
		"answers": ["あす",
		"あした"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明日香",
		"answers": ["あすか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飛鳥",
		"answers": ["あすか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小豆",
		"answers": ["あずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小豆餡",
		"answers": ["あずきあん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小豆粥",
		"answers": ["あずきがゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "翌檜",
		"answers": ["あすなろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅漢柏",
		"answers": ["あすなろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四阿",
		"answers": ["あずまや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叉倉",
		"answers": ["あぜくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "按察使",
		"answers": ["あぜち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "庵室",
		"answers": ["あぜち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "按察",
		"answers": ["あぜち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬酔木",
		"answers": ["あせび",
		"あしび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "汗疹",
		"answers": ["あせも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "汗肬",
		"answers": ["あせも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "汗疣",
		"answers": ["あせも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼所",
		"answers": ["あそこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼処",
		"answers": ["あそこ",
		"かしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朝臣",
		"answers": ["あそん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "化野",
		"answers": ["あだしの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "渾名",
		"answers": ["あだな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "諢名",
		"answers": ["あだな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "綽名",
		"answers": ["あだな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "可惜",
		"answers": ["あたら",
		"あったら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼方此方",
		"answers": ["あちこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿茶羅漬",
		"answers": ["あちゃらづけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼方",
		"answers": ["あちら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天晴",
		"answers": ["あっぱれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宛行",
		"answers": ["あてがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "充行",
		"answers": ["あてがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宛行扶持",
		"answers": ["あてがいぶち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "当所",
		"answers": ["あてど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貴人",
		"answers": ["あてびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花鶏",
		"answers": ["あとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恐惶",
		"answers": ["あなかしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鰻",
		"answers": ["あなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "足末",
		"answers": ["あなすえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貴女",
		"answers": ["あなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貴男",
		"answers": ["あなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貴方",
		"answers": ["あなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "痘痕",
		"answers": ["あばた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒家",
		"answers": ["あばらや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒屋",
		"answers": ["あばらや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "家鴨",
		"answers": ["あひる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿弗利加",
		"answers": ["あふりか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜弗利加",
		"answers": ["あふりか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "信天翁",
		"answers": ["あほうどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天児",
		"answers": ["あまがつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天倪",
		"answers": ["あまがつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天魚",
		"answers": ["あまご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天道",
		"answers": ["あまじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "許多",
		"answers": ["あまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "数多",
		"answers": ["あまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土常山",
		"answers": ["あまちゃ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "絞股藍",
		"answers": ["あまちゃづる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "淡漬",
		"answers": ["あまづけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "味漬",
		"answers": ["あまづけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甘野老",
		"answers": ["あまどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山慈姑",
		"answers": ["あまな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫菜",
		"answers": ["あまのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甘海苔",
		"answers": ["あまのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫菜",
		"answers": ["あまのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大葉藻",
		"answers": ["あまも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糠蝦",
		"answers": ["あみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "醬蝦",
		"answers": ["あみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "網結",
		"answers": ["あみすき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒竜江",
		"answers": ["あむーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄牛",
		"answers": ["あめうし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜墨利加",
		"answers": ["あめりか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜米利加",
		"answers": ["あめりか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水馬",
		"answers": ["あめんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水黽",
		"answers": ["あめんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漢氏",
		"answers": ["あやうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "怪士",
		"answers": ["あやかし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漢織",
		"answers": ["あやはとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漢人",
		"answers": ["あやひと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菖蒲",
		"answers": ["あやめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "年魚",
		"answers": ["あゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脚結",
		"answers": ["あゆい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "足結",
		"answers": ["あゆい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洗魚",
		"answers": ["あらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洗膾",
		"answers": ["あらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿剌吉",
		"answers": ["あらき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "新墾田",
		"answers": ["あらきだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒塊",
		"answers": ["あらくれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫羅欄花",
		"answers": ["あらせいとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桃花染",
		"answers": ["あらぞめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "退紅",
		"answers": ["あらぞめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "愛発関",
		"answers": ["あらちのせき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曠野",
		"answers": ["あらの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜拉毘亜",
		"answers": ["あらびあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜剌比亜",
		"answers": ["あらびあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苞苴",
		"answers": ["あらまき",
		"つと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒布",
		"answers": ["あらめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒和布",
		"answers": ["あらめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "所有",
		"answers": ["あらゆる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "所在",
		"answers": ["あらゆる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "在処",
		"answers": ["ありか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "在所",
		"answers": ["ありか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "存処",
		"answers": ["ありか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "食蟻獣",
		"answers": ["ありくい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒磯",
		"answers": ["ありそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土荊芥",
		"answers": ["ありたそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎刺",
		"answers": ["ありどおし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "擬蟻",
		"answers": ["ありもどき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主人",
		"answers": ["あるじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亜爾然丁",
		"answers": ["あるぜんちん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "有平糖",
		"answers": ["あるへいとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼是",
		"answers": ["あれこれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼此",
		"answers": ["あれこれ",
		"かれこれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "安房",
		"answers": ["あわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿波",
		"answers": ["あわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "周章る",
		"answers": ["あわてる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石決明",
		"answers": ["あわび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "望潮魚",
		"answers": ["いいだこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "許嫁",
		"answers": ["いいなずけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "許婚",
		"answers": ["いいなずけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飯粒",
		"answers": ["いいぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "家壁蝨",
		"answers": ["いえだに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五百",
		"answers": ["いお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "硫黄",
		"answers": ["いおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五十日",
		"answers": ["いか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "墨魚",
		"answers": ["いか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏賊",
		"answers": ["いか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何",
		"answers": ["いかが",
		"どう",
		"いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "笊籬",
		"answers": ["いかき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎垣",
		"answers": ["いがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沃懸地",
		"answers": ["いかけじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何様",
		"answers": ["いかさま",
		"いかよう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何様師",
		"answers": ["いかさまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉筋魚",
		"answers": ["いかなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何に",
		"answers": ["いかに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何物食い",
		"answers": ["いかものぐい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑鳩",
		"answers": ["いかる",
		"いかるが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如何",
		"answers": ["いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何若",
		"answers": ["いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何如",
		"answers": ["いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何奈",
		"answers": ["いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "奈何",
		"answers": ["いかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "髪菜",
		"answers": ["いぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海髪",
		"answers": ["いぎす",
		"おごのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生霊",
		"answers": ["いきすだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生魑魅",
		"answers": ["いきすだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寝穢い",
		"answers": ["いぎたない"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英吉利",
		"answers": ["いぎりす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "意気地",
		"answers": ["いくじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎串",
		"answers": ["いぐし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幾人",
		"answers": ["いくたり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "欠唇",
		"answers": ["いぐち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兎唇",
		"answers": ["いぐち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幾許",
		"answers": ["いくばく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幾何",
		"answers": ["いくばく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犠牲",
		"answers": ["いけにえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "居心地",
		"answers": ["いごこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岐嶷",
		"answers": ["いこよか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏魚",
		"answers": ["いさき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沙子",
		"answers": ["いさご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石蚕",
		"answers": ["いさごむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大角草",
		"answers": ["いささぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寝聡い",
		"answers": ["いざとい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "磯魚",
		"answers": ["いさな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細小魚",
		"answers": ["いさな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小魚",
		"answers": ["いさな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊弉諾尊",
		"answers": ["いざなぎのみこと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊邪那岐命",
		"answers": ["いざなぎのみこと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊弉冉尊",
		"answers": ["いざなみのみこと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊邪那美命",
		"answers": ["いざなみのみこと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑葉",
		"answers": ["いさは"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五十集",
		"answers": ["いさば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十六夜",
		"answers": ["いざよい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膝行る",
		"answers": ["いざる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水亀",
		"answers": ["いしがめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石椁",
		"answers": ["いしき",
		"いわき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻当",
		"answers": ["いしきあて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石塊",
		"answers": ["いしころ",
		"いしくれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石投",
		"answers": ["いしなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石子",
		"answers": ["いしなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石首魚",
		"answers": ["いしもち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅膏菜",
		"answers": ["いしもちそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "交喙",
		"answers": ["いすか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何処",
		"answers": ["いずこ",
		"いずく",
		"どこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "出石焼",
		"answers": ["いずしやき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚊母樹",
		"answers": ["いすのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和泉",
		"answers": ["いずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "出雲",
		"answers": ["いずも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "以色列",
		"answers": ["いすらえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竜蝦",
		"answers": ["いせえび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五十",
		"answers": ["いそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五十路",
		"answers": ["いそじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊曽保",
		"answers": ["いそっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊蘇普",
		"answers": ["いそっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊曾保",
		"answers": ["いそっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "磯蚯蚓",
		"answers": ["いそめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幼気",
		"answers": ["いたいけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "悪戯",
		"answers": ["いたずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木蓮子",
		"answers": ["いたび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊太利",
		"answers": ["いたりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "板山葵",
		"answers": ["いたわさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤檮",
		"answers": ["いちい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神巫",
		"answers": ["いちこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "覆盆子",
		"answers": ["いちご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "壱越調",
		"answers": ["いちこつちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "映日果",
		"answers": ["いちじく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無花果",
		"answers": ["いちじく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一八",
		"answers": ["いちはつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴟尾草",
		"answers": ["いちはつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳶尾",
		"answers": ["いちはつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳶尾",
		"answers": ["いちはつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄麻",
		"answers": ["いちび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青麻",
		"answers": ["いちび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿蹄草",
		"answers": ["いちやくそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴨脚樹",
		"answers": ["いちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "公孫樹",
		"answers": ["いちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銀杏",
		"answers": ["いちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銀杏返し",
		"answers": ["いちょうがえし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何時",
		"answers": ["いつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稜威",
		"answers": ["いつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従兄",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従姉",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従姉妹",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従弟",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従妹",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従兄弟",
		"answers": ["いとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糸蜻蛉",
		"answers": ["いととんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豆娘",
		"answers": ["いととんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糸魚",
		"answers": ["いとよ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金糸魚",
		"answers": ["いとよりだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金線魚",
		"answers": ["いとよりだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "田舎",
		"answers": ["いなか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鯔背銀杏",
		"answers": ["いなせいちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "因幡",
		"answers": ["いなば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛宿",
		"answers": ["いなみぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稲荷",
		"answers": ["いなり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粗榧",
		"answers": ["いぬがや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甎子苗",
		"answers": ["いぬくぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犬黄楊",
		"answers": ["いぬつげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犬の陰囊",
		"answers": ["いぬのふぐり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仙手欅",
		"answers": ["いぬぶな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅漢松",
		"answers": ["いぬまき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛膝",
		"answers": ["いのこずち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "居囃子",
		"answers": ["いばやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "息吹",
		"answers": ["いぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "気吹戸",
		"answers": ["いぶきど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "肬取木",
		"answers": ["いぼたのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水蠟樹",
		"answers": ["いぼたのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "疣取木",
		"answers": ["いぼたのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虫白蠟",
		"answers": ["いぼたろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水蠟樹蠟虫",
		"answers": ["いぼたろうむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "今際",
		"answers": ["いまわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎子",
		"answers": ["いむこ",
		"いみこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "妹兄",
		"answers": ["いもせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稲熱病",
		"answers": ["いもちびょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蠑螈",
		"answers": ["いもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥終",
		"answers": ["いやはて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥弥",
		"answers": ["いよいよ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "愈愈",
		"answers": ["いよいよ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺蛾",
		"answers": ["いらが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕁麻",
		"answers": ["いらくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺草",
		"answers": ["いらくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郎子",
		"answers": ["いらつこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郎女",
		"answers": ["いらつめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺虫",
		"answers": ["いらむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熬海鼠",
		"answers": ["いりこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海参",
		"answers": ["いりこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海豚",
		"answers": ["いるか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺青",
		"answers": ["いれずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "文身",
		"answers": ["いれずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "煎汁",
		"answers": ["いろり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沈子",
		"answers": ["いわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎人",
		"answers": ["いわいびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忌人",
		"answers": ["いわいびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忌瓮",
		"answers": ["いわいべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎瓮",
		"answers": ["いわいべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "磐座",
		"answers": ["いわくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岩清水",
		"answers": ["いわしみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石茸",
		"answers": ["いわたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦苣苔",
		"answers": ["いわたばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岩煙草",
		"answers": ["いわたばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岩魚",
		"answers": ["いわな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "嘉魚",
		"answers": ["いわな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岩棠子",
		"answers": ["いわなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石見",
		"answers": ["いわみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "所謂",
		"answers": ["いわゆる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岩曲",
		"answers": ["いわわだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊墨",
		"answers": ["いんく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英蘭土",
		"answers": ["いんぐらんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英倫",
		"answers": ["いんぐらんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眉児豆",
		"answers": ["いんげんまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菜豆",
		"answers": ["いんげんまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "印度",
		"answers": ["いんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "印籠決",
		"answers": ["いんろうじゃくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "維納",
		"answers": ["うぃーん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "回鶻",
		"answers": ["ういぐる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "初冠",
		"answers": ["ういこうぶり",
		"ういかむり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚河岸",
		"answers": ["うおがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "火酒",
		"answers": ["うぉっか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "倉稲魂",
		"answers": ["うかのみたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稲魂",
		"answers": ["うかのみたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "窺見",
		"answers": ["うかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斥候",
		"answers": ["うかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "親族",
		"answers": ["うから",
		"うがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拝所",
		"answers": ["うがんじゅ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泛子",
		"answers": ["うき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮子",
		"answers": ["うき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮萍",
		"answers": ["うきくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石斑魚",
		"answers": ["うぐい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祈狩",
		"answers": ["うけいがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五加木",
		"answers": ["うこぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五加",
		"answers": ["うこぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大人",
		"answers": ["うし",
		"おとな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "髻華",
		"answers": ["うず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雲珠",
		"answers": ["うず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "薄粧",
		"answers": ["うすけわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泡沫",
		"answers": ["うたかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仮寝",
		"answers": ["うたたね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雅楽頭",
		"answers": ["うたのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雅楽寮",
		"answers": ["うたりょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裲襠",
		"answers": ["うちかけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "団扇",
		"answers": ["うちわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "楊櫨木",
		"answers": ["うつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "卯木",
		"answers": ["うつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呆気者",
		"answers": ["うつけもの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "現身",
		"answers": ["うつしみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "現世",
		"answers": ["うつしよ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "現人",
		"answers": ["うつせみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "打棄る",
		"answers": ["うっちゃる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "打遣る",
		"answers": ["うっちゃる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "空五倍子",
		"answers": ["うつぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "空柴",
		"answers": ["うつぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鱓魚",
		"answers": ["うつぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猪籠草",
		"answers": ["うつぼかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独活",
		"answers": ["うど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "善知鳥",
		"answers": ["うとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "内舎人",
		"answers": ["うどねり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "首肯く",
		"answers": ["うなずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "項垂れる",
		"answers": ["うなだれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "池溝",
		"answers": ["うなて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海粟",
		"answers": ["うに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雲丹",
		"answers": ["うに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一角獣",
		"answers": ["うにこーる",
		"ゆにこーん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "己惚れる",
		"answers": ["うぬぼれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "自惚れる",
		"answers": ["うぬぼれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "采女",
		"answers": ["うねめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乳母",
		"answers": ["うば",
		"おんば",
		"めのと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "姥百合",
		"answers": ["うばゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕎麦葉貝母",
		"answers": ["うばゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "初心",
		"answers": ["うぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "産土",
		"answers": ["うぶすな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "産土神",
		"answers": ["うぶすながみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孕女",
		"answers": ["うぶめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "美味い",
		"answers": ["うまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熟寝",
		"answers": ["うまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "上手い",
		"answers": ["うまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苜蓿",
		"answers": ["うまごやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "連枝草",
		"answers": ["うまごやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "味酒",
		"answers": ["うまさけ",
		"うまざけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "美し国",
		"answers": ["うましくに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石女",
		"answers": ["うまずめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不生女",
		"answers": ["うまずめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬塞",
		"answers": ["うませ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬柵",
		"answers": ["うませ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毛茛",
		"answers": ["うまのあしがた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬の陰貝",
		"answers": ["うまのくぼがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬兜鈴",
		"answers": ["うまのすずくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "績麻",
		"answers": ["うみお",
		"うみそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竜葵",
		"answers": ["うみほおずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海酸漿",
		"answers": ["うみほおずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落霜紅",
		"answers": ["うめもどき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "卜兆",
		"answers": ["うらかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "心悲しい",
		"answers": ["うらがなしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "末殺",
		"answers": ["うらごけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浦塩斯徳",
		"answers": ["うらじおすとく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎掌",
		"answers": ["うらしまそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白梨樹",
		"answers": ["うらじろのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "卜書",
		"answers": ["うらぶみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "守瓜",
		"answers": ["うりばえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月蝿い",
		"answers": ["うるさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月蠅い",
		"answers": ["うるさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漆瘡",
		"answers": ["うるしかぶれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粳稲",
		"answers": ["うるしね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "得撫草",
		"answers": ["うるっぷそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "得撫島",
		"answers": ["うるっぷとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狼狽える",
		"answers": ["うろたえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "表着",
		"answers": ["うわぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "釉薬",
		"answers": ["うわぐすり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "譫言",
		"answers": ["うわごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "次妻",
		"answers": ["うわなり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "後妻",
		"answers": ["うわなり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟒蛇",
		"answers": ["うわばみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "外障",
		"answers": ["うわひ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "上不見桜",
		"answers": ["うわみずざくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮塵子",
		"answers": ["うんか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅糟粥",
		"answers": ["うんぞうがゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鷂魚",
		"answers": ["えい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "画韋",
		"answers": ["えがわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "愛迪生",
		"answers": ["えじそん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "埃及",
		"answers": ["えじぷと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "嘔吐く",
		"answers": ["えずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "似非",
		"answers": ["えせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "似而非",
		"answers": ["えせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狗母魚",
		"answers": ["えそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝦夷",
		"answers": ["えぞ",
		"えみし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "藍菊",
		"answers": ["えぞぎく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝦夷菊",
		"answers": ["えぞぎく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝦夷菫",
		"answers": ["えぞすみれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡菫菜",
		"answers": ["えぞすみれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岐路",
		"answers": ["えだみち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "干支",
		"answers": ["えと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "択捉",
		"answers": ["えとろふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胞衣",
		"answers": ["えな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金雀児",
		"answers": ["えにしだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金雀枝",
		"answers": ["えにしだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犬児",
		"answers": ["えのこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犬子",
		"answers": ["えのこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狗尾草",
		"answers": ["えのころぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛭子",
		"answers": ["えびす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吉方",
		"answers": ["えほう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏帽子",
		"answers": ["えぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "疫病",
		"answers": ["えやみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "疫病草",
		"answers": ["えやみぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瘧草",
		"answers": ["えやみぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "閻魔蟋蟀",
		"answers": ["えんまこおろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "美味しい",
		"answers": ["おいしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "追風",
		"answers": ["おいて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老次",
		"answers": ["おいなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花魁",
		"answers": ["おいらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花魁草",
		"answers": ["おいらんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老女",
		"answers": ["おうな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "近江",
		"answers": ["おうみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚍蜉",
		"answers": ["おおあり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大炊",
		"answers": ["おおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大炊寮",
		"answers": ["おおいりょう",
		"おおいのつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従祖父",
		"answers": ["おおおじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従祖母",
		"answers": ["おおおば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大鼓",
		"answers": ["おおかわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大塊",
		"answers": ["おおぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祖父",
		"answers": ["おおじ",
		"じい",
		"じじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大世帯",
		"answers": ["おおじょたい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毫州",
		"answers": ["おーすとらりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "濠太剌利",
		"answers": ["おーすとらりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒼鷹",
		"answers": ["おおたか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大殿油",
		"answers": ["おおとなぶら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祖母",
		"answers": ["おおば",
		"ばあ",
		"ばば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "車前",
		"answers": ["おおばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "車前草",
		"answers": ["おおばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大連",
		"answers": ["おおむらじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大凡",
		"answers": ["おおよそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "極光",
		"answers": ["おーろら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大曲",
		"answers": ["おおわだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大鋸屑",
		"answers": ["おがくず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "可笑しい",
		"answers": ["おかしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御菜",
		"answers": ["おかず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄心樹",
		"answers": ["おがたまのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御河童",
		"answers": ["おかっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "珍珠菜",
		"answers": ["おかとらのお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陸稲",
		"answers": ["おかぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女将",
		"answers": ["おかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御内儀",
		"answers": ["おかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麻殻",
		"answers": ["おがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清器",
		"answers": ["おかわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "隠岐",
		"answers": ["おき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "息嘯",
		"answers": ["おきそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白頭翁",
		"answers": ["おきなぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尺蠖",
		"answers": ["おぎむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御髪",
		"answers": ["おぐし",
		"みぐし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苧屑頭巾",
		"answers": ["おくそずきん",
		"ほくそずきん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "晩稲",
		"answers": ["おくて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "晩生",
		"answers": ["おくて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "童男",
		"answers": ["おぐな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "噫気",
		"answers": ["おくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "噯気",
		"answers": ["おくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金沸草",
		"answers": ["おぐるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋覆花",
		"answers": ["おぐるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白朮",
		"answers": ["おけら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白朮祭",
		"answers": ["おけらまつり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎魚",
		"answers": ["おこぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "江籬",
		"answers": ["おごのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御降",
		"answers": ["おさがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伯父",
		"answers": ["おじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叔父",
		"answers": ["おじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御祖父さん",
		"answers": ["おじいさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小父さん",
		"answers": ["おじさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴛鴦",
		"answers": ["おしどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "襁褓",
		"answers": ["おしめ",
		"むつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御洒落",
		"answers": ["おしゃれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白粉",
		"answers": ["おしろい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白粉花",
		"answers": ["おしろいばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫茉莉",
		"answers": ["おしろいばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "嬋媛",
		"answers": ["おそよか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御母様",
		"answers": ["おたあさま",
		"おたたさま",
		"おかあさま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝌蚪",
		"answers": ["おたまじゃくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御為倒し",
		"answers": ["おためごかし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遠方",
		"answers": ["おちかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遠近",
		"answers": ["おちこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彼方此方",
		"answers": ["おちこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "零落れる",
		"answers": ["おちぶれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落魄れる",
		"answers": ["おちぶれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "変若水",
		"answers": ["おちみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "復水",
		"answers": ["おちみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落人",
		"answers": ["おちゅうど",
		"おちうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛津",
		"answers": ["おっくすふぉーど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御汁",
		"answers": ["おつけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仰有る",
		"answers": ["おっしゃる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "追而書",
		"answers": ["おってがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "良人",
		"answers": ["おっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海狗",
		"answers": ["おっとせい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膃肭臍",
		"answers": ["おっとせい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御頭",
		"answers": ["おつむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小連翹",
		"answers": ["おとぎりそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "男郎子",
		"answers": ["おとこえし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "敗醬",
		"answers": ["おとこえし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "俠気",
		"answers": ["おとこぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "男伊達",
		"answers": ["おとこだて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大殿",
		"answers": ["おとど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大臣",
		"answers": ["おとど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一昨日",
		"answers": ["おととい",
		"おとつい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一昨年",
		"answers": ["おととし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "少女",
		"answers": ["おとめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "媒鳥",
		"answers": ["おとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野芝麻",
		"answers": ["おどりこそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荊棘",
		"answers": ["おどろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巻耳",
		"answers": ["おなもみ",
		"みみなぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬼蜻蜓",
		"answers": ["おにやんま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巻丹",
		"answers": ["おにゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬼百合",
		"answers": ["おにゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "各各",
		"answers": ["おのおの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叔母",
		"answers": ["おば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伯母",
		"answers": ["おば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御祖母さん",
		"answers": ["おばあさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄漿",
		"answers": ["おはぐろ",
		"かね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十八番",
		"answers": ["おはこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小母さん",
		"answers": ["おばさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "男茎",
		"answers": ["おはせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛筋草",
		"answers": ["おひしば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大鮃",
		"answers": ["おひょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅樹",
		"answers": ["おひるぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "未通女",
		"answers": ["おぼこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御火焼",
		"answers": ["おほたき",
		"おひたき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御虎子",
		"answers": ["おまる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御巡りさん",
		"answers": ["おまわりさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小斎",
		"answers": ["おみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小忌",
		"answers": ["おみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大神酒",
		"answers": ["おみき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御神酒",
		"answers": ["おみき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御神籤",
		"answers": ["おみくじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小忌衣",
		"answers": ["おみごろも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女郎花",
		"answers": ["おみなえし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臆虫",
		"answers": ["おめむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御父様",
		"answers": ["おもうさま",
		"おとうさま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "以為",
		"answers": ["おもえらく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "面繫",
		"answers": ["おもがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "面懸",
		"answers": ["おもがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "面瘡",
		"answers": ["おもくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沢瀉",
		"answers": ["おもだか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玩具",
		"answers": ["おもちゃ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "重傷",
		"answers": ["おもで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "万年青",
		"answers": ["おもと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "母屋",
		"answers": ["おもや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "母家",
		"answers": ["おもや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女形",
		"answers": ["おやま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猩猩",
		"answers": ["おらんうーたん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿蘭陀",
		"answers": ["おらんだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿蘭陀",
		"answers": ["おらんだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和蘭",
		"answers": ["おらんだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿利襪",
		"answers": ["おりーぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "阿利布",
		"answers": ["おりーぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "自鳴琴",
		"answers": ["おるごーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "下風",
		"answers": ["おろし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大蛇",
		"answers": ["おろち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御衣",
		"answers": ["おんぞ",
		"みけし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乳母日傘",
		"answers": ["おんばひがさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "母さん",
		"answers": ["かあさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲斐",
		"answers": ["かい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲斐甲斐しい",
		"answers": ["かいがいしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲斐絹",
		"answers": ["かいき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匙笥",
		"answers": ["かいげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "搔笥",
		"answers": ["かいげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲斐性",
		"answers": ["かいしょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "垣外",
		"answers": ["かいと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "垣内",
		"answers": ["かいと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花仙",
		"answers": ["かいどう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貝寄風",
		"answers": ["かいよせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梅花皮",
		"answers": ["かいらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "穎割れ",
		"answers": ["かいわれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頴割れ",
		"answers": ["かいわれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏冠木",
		"answers": ["かえで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "槭楓",
		"answers": ["かえで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛙手",
		"answers": ["かえで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加加阿",
		"answers": ["かかお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "母様",
		"answers": ["かかさま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿驚",
		"answers": ["かかし",
		"かがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "案山子",
		"answers": ["かかし",
		"かがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大蚊",
		"answers": ["ががんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牡蠣",
		"answers": ["かき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜若",
		"answers": ["かきつばた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "燕子花",
		"answers": ["かきつばた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬蹄草",
		"answers": ["かきどおし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "連銭草",
		"answers": ["かきどおし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉤状",
		"answers": ["かぎなり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "民部",
		"answers": ["かきべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "部曲",
		"answers": ["かきべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陽炎",
		"answers": ["かぎろい",
		"かげろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "堅磐",
		"answers": ["かきわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "混合酒",
		"answers": ["かくてる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如此",
		"answers": ["かくのごとし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如斯",
		"answers": ["かくのごとし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜夫魚",
		"answers": ["かくぶつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神楽",
		"answers": ["かぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神楽月",
		"answers": ["かぐらづき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰日向",
		"answers": ["かげひなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "欠片",
		"answers": ["かけら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜉蝣",
		"answers": ["かげろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜻蛉",
		"answers": ["かげろう",
		"とんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水手",
		"answers": ["かこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水夫",
		"answers": ["かこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "駕籠",
		"answers": ["かご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "駕籠舁",
		"answers": ["かごかき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "託言",
		"answers": ["かごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "挿頭す",
		"answers": ["かざす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "汗衫",
		"answers": ["かざみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河岸",
		"answers": ["かし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鍛冶",
		"answers": ["かじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜父魚",
		"answers": ["かじか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金襖子",
		"answers": ["かじかがえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旗魚",
		"answers": ["かじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "搗布",
		"answers": ["かじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄鶏",
		"answers": ["かしわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膳夫",
		"answers": ["かしわで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拍手",
		"answers": ["かしわで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓦斯",
		"answers": ["がす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主計頭",
		"answers": ["かずえのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "被衣",
		"answers": ["かずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飛白",
		"answers": ["かすり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石陰子",
		"answers": ["かせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿杖",
		"answers": ["かせづえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "父母",
		"answers": ["かぞいろは"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和雑膾",
		"answers": ["かぞうなます"]
	},
	{
		"question": "方人",
		"answers": ["かたうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "片方",
		"answers": ["かたえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旁旁",
		"answers": ["かたがた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "気質",
		"answers": ["かたぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "醇酒",
		"answers": ["かたざけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "固唾",
		"answers": ["かたず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝸牛",
		"answers": ["かたつむり",
		"でんでんむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "結政所",
		"answers": ["かたなしどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酢漿草",
		"answers": ["かたばみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酸漿草",
		"answers": ["かたばみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳩酸草",
		"answers": ["かたばみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "帷子",
		"answers": ["かたびら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加答児",
		"answers": ["かたる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川太郎",
		"answers": ["がたろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "徒歩",
		"answers": ["かち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "歩射",
		"answers": ["かちゆみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松魚",
		"answers": ["かつお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "堅魚",
		"answers": ["かつお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "堅魚木",
		"answers": ["かつおぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "腸線",
		"answers": ["がっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河童",
		"answers": ["かっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "首途",
		"answers": ["かどで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "看督長",
		"answers": ["かどのおさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加持力",
		"answers": ["かとりっく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勾引かす",
		"answers": ["かどわかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "釜殿",
		"answers": ["かなえどの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "方頭魚",
		"answers": ["かながしら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "火魚",
		"answers": ["かながしら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金巾",
		"answers": ["かなきん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加奈陀",
		"answers": ["かなだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金鉗",
		"answers": ["かなばし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛇舅母",
		"answers": ["かなへび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金椀",
		"answers": ["かなまり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金糸雀",
		"answers": ["かなりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海金砂",
		"answers": ["かにくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "擬蠍",
		"answers": ["かにむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曲尺",
		"answers": ["かねじゃく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕪菁",
		"answers": ["かぶ",
		"かぶら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臭橙",
		"answers": ["かぶす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頭槌の大刀",
		"answers": ["かぶつちのたち",
		"くぶつちのたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頭椎の大刀",
		"answers": ["かぶつちのたち",
		"くぶつちのたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鱟魚",
		"answers": ["かぶとがに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鏑矢",
		"answers": ["かぶらや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南瓜",
		"answers": ["かぼちゃ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香蒲",
		"answers": ["がま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟷螂",
		"answers": ["かまきり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螳螂",
		"answers": ["かまきり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梭魚",
		"answers": ["かます"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梭子魚",
		"answers": ["かます"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒲魚",
		"answers": ["かまとと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長官",
		"answers": ["かみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "剃刀",
		"answers": ["かみそり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "霹靂",
		"answers": ["かみとき",
		"かみとけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加密爾列",
		"answers": ["かみるれ",
		"かもみーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "椿象",
		"answers": ["かめむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "氈瓜",
		"answers": ["かもうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羚羊",
		"answers": ["かもしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "氈鹿",
		"answers": ["かもしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴨嘴獣",
		"answers": ["かものはし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掃部",
		"answers": ["かもん",
		"かもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚊帳",
		"answers": ["かや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚊帳吊草",
		"answers": ["かやつりぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掛落",
		"answers": ["から"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掛絡",
		"answers": ["から"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掛羅",
		"answers": ["から"]
	},
	{
		"question": "揶揄う",
		"answers": ["からかう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "響尾蛇",
		"answers": ["がらがらへび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "厳器",
		"answers": ["からくしげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "機関",
		"answers": ["からくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哈剌和林",
		"answers": ["からこるむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和林",
		"answers": ["からこるむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和寧",
		"answers": ["からこるむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾鮭",
		"answers": ["からざけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芥子",
		"answers": ["からし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芥子菜",
		"answers": ["からしな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "硝子",
		"answers": ["がらす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老鴉瓜",
		"answers": ["からすうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "王瓜",
		"answers": ["からすうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚌貝",
		"answers": ["からすがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾咳",
		"answers": ["からせき",
		"からぜき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "身体",
		"answers": ["からだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "枳殻",
		"answers": ["からたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百両金",
		"answers": ["からたちばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾っ風",
		"answers": ["からっかぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "空梅雨",
		"answers": ["からつゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "権衡",
		"answers": ["からばかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "屍櫃",
		"answers": ["からひつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾拭き",
		"answers": ["からぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "樺太",
		"answers": ["からふと",
		"さはりん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落葉松",
		"answers": ["からまつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苧麻",
		"answers": ["からむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苟且",
		"answers": ["かりそめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加州",
		"answers": ["かりふぉるにあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青茅",
		"answers": ["かりやす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猟人",
		"answers": ["かりゅうど",
		"かりうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狩人",
		"answers": ["かりゅうど",
		"かりうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花梨",
		"answers": ["かりん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花櫚",
		"answers": ["かりん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "軽衫",
		"answers": ["かるさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "骨牌",
		"answers": ["かるた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "骨牒",
		"answers": ["かるた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "歌留多",
		"answers": ["かるた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "加留多",
		"answers": ["かるた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮石糖",
		"answers": ["かるめら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泡糖",
		"answers": ["かるめら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲乙",
		"answers": ["かるめる",
		"かりめり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "王餘魚",
		"answers": ["かれい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾飯",
		"answers": ["かれいい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川獺",
		"answers": ["かわうそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水獺",
		"answers": ["かわうそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川螻蛄",
		"answers": ["かわげら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為替",
		"answers": ["かわせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水狗",
		"answers": ["かわせみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚狗",
		"answers": ["かわせみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚虎",
		"answers": ["かわせみ",
		"はりせんぼん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河内",
		"answers": ["かわち",
		"はのい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河貝子",
		"answers": ["かわにな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水楊",
		"answers": ["かわやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河原",
		"answers": ["かわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川原",
		"answers": ["かわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川曲",
		"answers": ["かわわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜衡",
		"answers": ["かんあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "袋鼠",
		"answers": ["かんがるー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主神",
		"answers": ["かんざね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寒復習",
		"answers": ["かんざらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾陀羅",
		"answers": ["がんだーら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "健駄羅",
		"answers": ["がんだーら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "強盗頭巾",
		"answers": ["がんどうずきん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "惟神",
		"answers": ["かんながら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "随神",
		"answers": ["かんながら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貫木",
		"answers": ["かんぬき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柬蒲塞",
		"answers": ["かんぼじあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柬埔寨",
		"answers": ["かんぼじあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "懸鉤子",
		"answers": ["きいちご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木尺",
		"answers": ["きがね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木蠧虫",
		"answers": ["きくいむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木蠹虫",
		"answers": ["きくいむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "聞道",
		"answers": ["きくならく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "聞説",
		"answers": ["きくならく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菊の被綿",
		"answers": ["きくのきせわた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木耳",
		"answers": ["きくらげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "樵夫",
		"answers": ["きこり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "段段",
		"answers": ["ぎざぎざ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刻刻",
		"answers": ["ぎざぎざ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扁螺",
		"answers": ["きさご",
		"きしゃご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細螺",
		"answers": ["きさご",
		"きしゃご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細瓮",
		"answers": ["きさべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如月",
		"answers": ["きさらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "更衣",
		"answers": ["きさらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木淡",
		"answers": ["きざわし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素地",
		"answers": ["きじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊蹄",
		"answers": ["ぎしぎし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長寿花",
		"answers": ["きずいせん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "著長",
		"answers": ["きせなが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "煙管",
		"answers": ["きせる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "被綿",
		"answers": ["きせわた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生蕎麦",
		"answers": ["きそば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "着衣始",
		"answers": ["きそはじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "堅塩",
		"answers": ["きたし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蓄縮",
		"answers": ["きっしく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毬杖",
		"answers": ["ぎっちょう",
		"ぎちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毬打",
		"answers": ["ぎっちょう",
		"ぎちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "啄木鳥",
		"answers": ["きつつき",
		"けら",
		"けらきつつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "急度",
		"answers": ["きっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "爵牀",
		"answers": ["きつねのまご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狐日和",
		"answers": ["きつねびより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "規那",
		"answers": ["きな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "半銭",
		"answers": ["きなか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "焦臭い",
		"answers": ["きなくさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "規尼涅",
		"answers": ["きにーね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仙人帽",
		"answers": ["きぬがさたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "衣被",
		"answers": ["きぬかつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "後朝",
		"answers": ["きぬぎぬ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "昨日",
		"answers": ["きのう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独脚蜂",
		"answers": ["きばち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "急焼",
		"answers": ["きびしょ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生皮苧",
		"answers": ["きびそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黍魚子",
		"answers": ["きびなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吉備奈仔",
		"answers": ["きびなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旌節花",
		"answers": ["きぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木五倍子",
		"answers": ["きぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "通条花",
		"answers": ["きぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫萼",
		"answers": ["ぎぼうし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "擬宝珠",
		"answers": ["ぎぼうし",
		"ぎぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉簪花",
		"answers": ["ぎぼうし",
		"ぎぼし",
		"たまのかんざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生真面目",
		"answers": ["きまじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄身時雨",
		"answers": ["きみしぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沈菜",
		"answers": ["きむち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄紫茸",
		"answers": ["きむらたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "肌理",
		"answers": ["きめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾煎り",
		"answers": ["きもいり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脚榻",
		"answers": ["きゃたつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "妓夫",
		"answers": ["ぎゅう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "気宇仙",
		"answers": ["きゅうせん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡瓜",
		"answers": ["きゅうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄瓜",
		"answers": ["きゅうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "今日",
		"answers": ["きょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "経帷子",
		"answers": ["きょうかたびら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "軽軽",
		"answers": ["きょうきょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "姉妹",
		"answers": ["きょうだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "姉弟",
		"answers": ["きょうだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "今日日",
		"answers": ["きょうび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪花菜",
		"answers": ["きらず",
		"おから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雲母",
		"answers": ["きらら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金瘡小草",
		"answers": ["きらんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螽斯",
		"answers": ["きりぎりす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "希臘",
		"answers": ["ぎりしゃ",
		"ぎりしあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "基督",
		"answers": ["きりすと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "切麻",
		"answers": ["きりぬさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尾能",
		"answers": ["きりのう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "布地",
		"answers": ["きれじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金海鼠",
		"answers": ["きんこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "光参",
		"answers": ["きんこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅南瓜",
		"answers": ["きんとうが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青蠅",
		"answers": ["きんばえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒟醬",
		"answers": ["きんま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒟醬塗",
		"answers": ["きんまぬり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水鶏",
		"answers": ["くいな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秧鶏",
		"answers": ["くいな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "威霊仙",
		"answers": ["くがいそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陸路",
		"answers": ["くがじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "探湯",
		"answers": ["くかたち",
		"くがたち",
		"くかだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盟神探湯",
		"answers": ["くかたち",
		"くがたち",
		"くかだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "誓湯",
		"answers": ["くかたち",
		"くがたち",
		"くかだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "傀儡子",
		"answers": ["くぐつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "傀儡",
		"answers": ["くぐつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漏穴",
		"answers": ["くけあな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匿穴",
		"answers": ["くけあな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臭牡丹樹",
		"answers": ["くさぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海州常山",
		"answers": ["くさぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白屈菜",
		"answers": ["くさのおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草雲雀",
		"answers": ["くさひばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草木瓜",
		"answers": ["くさぼけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草連玉",
		"answers": ["くされだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄連花",
		"answers": ["くされだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "典薬頭",
		"answers": ["くすりのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小角",
		"answers": ["くだのふえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草臥れる",
		"answers": ["くたびれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "果物",
		"answers": ["くだもの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百済",
		"answers": ["くだら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瀉腹",
		"answers": ["くだりばら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巵子",
		"answers": ["くちなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "卮子",
		"answers": ["くちなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山梔子",
		"answers": ["くちなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "口下手",
		"answers": ["くちべた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "聒聒児",
		"answers": ["くつわむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恭仁京",
		"answers": ["くにきょう",
		"くにのみやつこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地祇",
		"answers": ["くにつかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香橘",
		"answers": ["くねんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葉椀",
		"answers": ["くぼて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熊谷草",
		"answers": ["くまがいそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熊啄木鳥",
		"answers": ["くまげら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山白竹",
		"answers": ["くまざさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "奠稲",
		"answers": ["くましね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "角鷹",
		"answers": ["くまたか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛇藤",
		"answers": ["くまやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山藤",
		"answers": ["くまやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡頽子",
		"answers": ["ぐみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜘蛛",
		"answers": ["くも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜘蛛膜下出血",
		"answers": ["くもまくかしゅっけつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "口惜しい",
		"answers": ["くやしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水母",
		"answers": ["くらげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海月",
		"answers": ["くらげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "倶楽部",
		"answers": ["くらぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "俱楽部",
		"answers": ["くらぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦参",
		"answers": ["くらら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "内蔵寮",
		"answers": ["くらりょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "捏色",
		"answers": ["くりいろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "反転",
		"answers": ["くるべき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呉桃",
		"answers": ["くるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡桃",
		"answers": ["くるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山胡桃",
		"answers": ["くるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曲輪",
		"answers": ["くるわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牙床",
		"answers": ["くれどこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "懐香",
		"answers": ["くれのおも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呉母",
		"answers": ["くれのおも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呉織",
		"answers": ["くれはとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呉服",
		"answers": ["くれはとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玄人",
		"answers": ["くろうと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蔵人",
		"answers": ["くろうど",
		"くらんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼠李",
		"answers": ["くろうめもどき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒衣",
		"answers": ["くろご",
		"くろこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒鵐",
		"answers": ["くろじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏竹",
		"answers": ["くろちく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桄榔子",
		"answers": ["くろつぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桄榔",
		"answers": ["くろつぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒南風",
		"answers": ["くろはえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒檜",
		"answers": ["くろべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏豆",
		"answers": ["くろまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏樟",
		"answers": ["くろもじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉤樟",
		"answers": ["くろもじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏芋",
		"answers": ["くわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "慈姑",
		"answers": ["くわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野蚕",
		"answers": ["くわご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "钁丁",
		"answers": ["くわよぼろ",
		"くわよほろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "窩主",
		"answers": ["けいず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "窩主買",
		"answers": ["けいずかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏冠",
		"answers": ["けいとう",
		"とかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "今朝",
		"answers": ["けさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "罌粟",
		"answers": ["けし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "景色",
		"answers": ["けしき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毛布",
		"answers": ["けっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荷包牡丹",
		"answers": ["けまんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螻蛄",
		"answers": ["けら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟹足腫",
		"answers": ["けろいど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "化粧",
		"answers": ["けわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "翹揺",
		"answers": ["げんげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫雲英",
		"answers": ["げんげ",
		"れんげそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竜蝨",
		"answers": ["げんごろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "剣橋",
		"answers": ["けんぶりっじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臥亜",
		"answers": ["ごあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此奴",
		"answers": ["こいつ",
		"こやつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "庶幾う",
		"answers": ["こいねがう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "髪際",
		"answers": ["こうぎわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柑子",
		"answers": ["こうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勘事",
		"answers": ["こうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香匙",
		"answers": ["こうすくい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "革茸",
		"answers": ["こうたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皮茸",
		"answers": ["こうたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅蕈",
		"answers": ["こうたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小女子",
		"answers": ["こうなご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河骨",
		"answers": ["こうほね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "川骨",
		"answers": ["こうほね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊傘",
		"answers": ["こうもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝙蝠",
		"answers": ["こうもり",
		"かわほり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙屋紙",
		"answers": ["こうやがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "肥担桶",
		"answers": ["こえたご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "高加索",
		"answers": ["こーかさす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀躍",
		"answers": ["こおどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "珈琲",
		"answers": ["こーひー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沙蚕",
		"answers": ["ごかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金亀子",
		"answers": ["こがねむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "合子草",
		"answers": ["ごきづる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏木",
		"answers": ["こくたん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "越橘",
		"answers": ["こけもも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木屑",
		"answers": ["こけら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小啄木鳥",
		"answers": ["こげら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苔竜胆",
		"answers": ["こけりんどう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此所",
		"answers": ["ここ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此処",
		"answers": ["ここ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "心地",
		"answers": ["ここち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九十",
		"answers": ["ここのそじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九十路",
		"answers": ["ここのそじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哥薩克",
		"answers": ["こさっく",
		"こざっく",
		"かざーく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巾子",
		"answers": ["こじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金漆",
		"answers": ["こしあぶら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巾子形",
		"answers": ["こじかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五十雀",
		"answers": ["ごじゅうから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豆汁",
		"answers": ["ごじる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋桜",
		"answers": ["こすもす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瞽女",
		"answers": ["ごぜ",
		"ごじょ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小太刀",
		"answers": ["こだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此度",
		"answers": ["こたび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拘泥る",
		"answers": ["こだわる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛尾魚",
		"answers": ["こち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "東風",
		"answers": ["こち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此方人等",
		"answers": ["こちとら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "此方",
		"answers": ["こちら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小晦日",
		"answers": ["こつごもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊杯",
		"answers": ["こっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "特牛",
		"answers": ["こというし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "琴柱",
		"answers": ["ことじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "筝柱",
		"answers": ["ことじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "部領",
		"answers": ["ことり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小半",
		"answers": ["こなから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二合半",
		"answers": ["こなから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小水葱",
		"answers": ["こなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴨舌草",
		"answers": ["こなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小茄子",
		"answers": ["こなすび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木末",
		"answers": ["こぬれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "練墨",
		"answers": ["こねずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小腹",
		"answers": ["このかみ",
		"こがみ",
		"ほがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鼠子",
		"answers": ["このこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兄部",
		"answers": ["このこうべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "側柏",
		"answers": ["このてがしわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木の葉時雨",
		"answers": ["このはしぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木の葉木菟",
		"answers": ["このはずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兄鷂",
		"answers": ["このり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鼠腸",
		"answers": ["このわた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小鉤",
		"answers": ["こはぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木皮",
		"answers": ["こはだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小春日和",
		"answers": ["こはるびより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "戈壁",
		"answers": ["ごび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "辛夷",
		"answers": ["こぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾分",
		"answers": ["こぶん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾児",
		"answers": ["こぶん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独楽",
		"answers": ["こま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "氷下魚",
		"answers": ["こまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "氷魚",
		"answers": ["こまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "高麗鼠",
		"answers": ["こまねずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独楽鼠",
		"answers": ["こまねずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒参",
		"answers": ["ごまのはぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玄参",
		"answers": ["ごまのはぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "高麗笛",
		"answers": ["こまぶえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "塵芥虫",
		"answers": ["ごみむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芥虫",
		"answers": ["ごみむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "歩行虫",
		"answers": ["ごみむし",
		"おさむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "護謨",
		"answers": ["ごむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟀谷",
		"answers": ["こめかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "顳顬",
		"answers": ["こめかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熊川",
		"answers": ["こもがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "今宵",
		"answers": ["こよい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙捻",
		"answers": ["こより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙撚",
		"answers": ["こより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙縒",
		"answers": ["こより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石伏魚",
		"answers": ["ごり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎列剌",
		"answers": ["これら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "破落戸",
		"answers": ["ごろつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無頼",
		"answers": ["ごろつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "転寝",
		"answers": ["ごろね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哥倫比亜",
		"answers": ["ころんびあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恐恐",
		"answers": ["こわごわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小童",
		"answers": ["こわっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "強面",
		"answers": ["こわもて",
		"こわおもて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "混擬土",
		"answers": ["こんくりーと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "濃漿",
		"answers": ["こんず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野鴉椿",
		"answers": ["ごんずい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "健児",
		"answers": ["こんでい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巨頭鯨",
		"answers": ["ごんどうくじら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金平糖",
		"answers": ["こんぺいとう",
		"こんぺいとー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "搾菜",
		"answers": ["ざーさい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋剣",
		"answers": ["さーべる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋刀",
		"answers": ["さーべる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皁莢",
		"answers": ["さいかち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "骰子",
		"answers": ["さいころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "賽子",
		"answers": ["さいころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "西貢",
		"answers": ["さいごん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柴棍",
		"answers": ["さいごん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "騒騒",
		"answers": ["さいさい",
		"さえさえ",
		"ざわざわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木椎",
		"answers": ["さいづち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "道祖土焼",
		"answers": ["さいとやき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "割符",
		"answers": ["さいふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貲布",
		"answers": ["さいみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細布",
		"answers": ["さいみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "道祖神",
		"answers": ["さえのかみ",
		"さいのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "楊桐",
		"answers": ["さかき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "造酒児",
		"answers": ["さかつこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "造酒童女",
		"answers": ["さかつこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掌酒",
		"answers": ["さかびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酒祝",
		"answers": ["さかほがい",
		"さかほかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酒寿",
		"answers": ["さかほがい",
		"さかほかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "逆戟",
		"answers": ["さかまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "相模",
		"answers": ["さがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "逆虎落",
		"answers": ["さかもがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿砦",
		"answers": ["さかもぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "月代",
		"answers": ["さかやき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "月額",
		"answers": ["さかやき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主典",
		"answers": ["さかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一昨昨日",
		"answers": ["さきおととい",
		"さきおとつい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一昨昨年",
		"answers": ["さきおととし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三枝",
		"answers": ["さきくさ",
		"さいぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三毬杖",
		"answers": ["さぎちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幸魂",
		"answers": ["さきみたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "防人",
		"answers": ["さきもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三狐神",
		"answers": ["さぐし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桜府",
		"answers": ["さくらめんと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桜桃",
		"answers": ["さくらんぼう",
		"さくらんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柘榴",
		"answers": ["ざくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石榴",
		"answers": ["ざくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "安石榴",
		"answers": ["ざくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粟米草",
		"answers": ["ざくろそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石榴草",
		"answers": ["ざくろそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雑魚",
		"answers": ["ざこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青箭魚",
		"answers": ["さごし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雑魚寝",
		"answers": ["ざこね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沙穀椰子",
		"answers": ["さごやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小竹",
		"answers": ["ささ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹筒",
		"answers": ["ささえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小筒",
		"answers": ["ささえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拳螺",
		"answers": ["さざえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拳螺",
		"answers": ["さざえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "栄螺",
		"answers": ["さざえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大角豆",
		"answers": ["ささげ",
		"ささぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "篠竹",
		"answers": ["ささたけ",
		"すずたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小波",
		"answers": ["さざなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細雪",
		"answers": ["ささめゆき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "私語く",
		"answers": ["ささやく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細石",
		"answers": ["さざれいし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山茶花",
		"answers": ["さざんか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茶梅",
		"answers": ["さざんか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺亀虫",
		"answers": ["さしがめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺椿象",
		"answers": ["さしがめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銚子",
		"answers": ["さしなべ",
		"さすなべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "指焼草",
		"answers": ["さしもぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流石",
		"answers": ["さすが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流離う",
		"answers": ["さすらう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猟夫",
		"answers": ["さつお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猟男",
		"answers": ["さつお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月",
		"answers": ["さつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皐月",
		"answers": ["さつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月晴",
		"answers": ["さつきばれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月闇",
		"answers": ["さつきやみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拶双魚",
		"answers": ["さっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甘藷",
		"answers": ["さつまいも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小網",
		"answers": ["さで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "里曲",
		"answers": ["さとみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "里廻",
		"answers": ["さとみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "里回",
		"answers": ["さとみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真田虫",
		"answers": ["さなだむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "条虫",
		"answers": ["さなだむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "早苗饗",
		"answers": ["さなぶり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南五倍子",
		"answers": ["さねかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真葛",
		"answers": ["さねかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酸棗",
		"answers": ["さねぶとなつめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青花魚",
		"answers": ["さば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青魚",
		"answers": ["さば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月蝿",
		"answers": ["さばえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月蠅",
		"answers": ["さばえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡銅器",
		"answers": ["さはり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "響銅",
		"answers": ["さはり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荒鮎",
		"answers": ["さびあゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宿鮎",
		"answers": ["さびあゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "方済各",
		"answers": ["ざびえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "番紅花",
		"answers": ["さふらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仙人掌",
		"answers": ["さぼてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "覇王樹",
		"answers": ["さぼてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "然程",
		"answers": ["さほど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朱欒",
		"answers": ["ざぼん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香欒",
		"answers": ["ざぼん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "然迄",
		"answers": ["さまで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彷徨う",
		"answers": ["さまよう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五月雨",
		"answers": ["さみだれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白眼",
		"answers": ["さめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遮莫",
		"answers": ["さもあらばあれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匣鉢",
		"answers": ["さや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素湯",
		"answers": ["さゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白湯",
		"answers": ["さゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小百合",
		"answers": ["さゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "然様",
		"answers": ["さよう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "然様なら",
		"answers": ["さようなら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "針魚",
		"answers": ["さより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細魚",
		"answers": ["さより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "復習う",
		"answers": ["さらう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浅甕",
		"answers": ["さらけ",
		"さらげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "更紗",
		"answers": ["さらさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盤秤",
		"answers": ["さらばかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粗目",
		"answers": ["ざらめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粗目雪",
		"answers": ["ざらめゆき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝲蛄",
		"answers": ["ざりがに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猿麻峠",
		"answers": ["さるおがせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松蘿",
		"answers": ["さるおがせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "撒爾沙",
		"answers": ["さるさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "撒児沙",
		"answers": ["さるさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "怕痒樹",
		"answers": ["さるすべり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百日紅",
		"answers": ["さるすべり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫薇",
		"answers": ["さるすべり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "笊蕎麦",
		"answers": ["ざるそば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡孫眼",
		"answers": ["さるのこしかけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猿真似",
		"answers": ["さるまね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "髑髏",
		"answers": ["されこうべ",
		"しゃれこうべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狗舌草",
		"answers": ["さわおぐるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山梗葉",
		"answers": ["さわぎきょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寿光木",
		"answers": ["さわぐるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沢胡桃",
		"answers": ["さわぐるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皿鉢",
		"answers": ["さわち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花柏",
		"answers": ["さわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弱檜",
		"answers": ["さわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬鮫魚",
		"answers": ["さわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜀椒",
		"answers": ["さんしょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "槐葉蘋",
		"answers": ["さんしょうも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桟俵法師",
		"answers": ["さんだらぼっち",
		"さんだらぼうし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桑港",
		"answers": ["さんふらんしすこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秋刀魚",
		"answers": ["さんま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "明明後日",
		"answers": ["しあさって"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香蕈",
		"answers": ["しいたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬼頭魚",
		"answers": ["しいら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勒魚",
		"answers": ["しいら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沙翁",
		"answers": ["しぇーくすぴあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "悄悄",
		"answers": ["しおしお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛尾菜",
		"answers": ["しおで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四方手",
		"answers": ["しおで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "望潮",
		"answers": ["しおまねき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "云爾",
		"answers": ["しかいう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "市俄古",
		"answers": ["しかご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "云云",
		"answers": ["しかじか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "直足袋",
		"answers": ["じかたび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫香楽宮",
		"answers": ["しがらきのみや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "信楽焼",
		"answers": ["しがらやき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "磯城",
		"answers": ["しき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甃石",
		"answers": ["しきいし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為着せ",
		"answers": ["しきせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "重播",
		"answers": ["しきまき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "時雨",
		"answers": ["しぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "時雨煮",
		"answers": ["しぐれに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "時化",
		"answers": ["しけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "淑景舎",
		"answers": ["しげいしゃ",
		"しげいさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "重籐",
		"answers": ["しげとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻籠",
		"answers": ["しこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竜爪稗",
		"answers": ["しこくびえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "色丹",
		"answers": ["しこたん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "色丹草",
		"answers": ["しこたんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無言",
		"answers": ["しじま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "静寂",
		"answers": ["しじま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小灰蝶",
		"answers": ["しじみちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "笑靨花",
		"answers": ["しじみばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柳葉魚",
		"answers": ["ししゃも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四十雀",
		"answers": ["しじゅうから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "縮羅",
		"answers": ["しじら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "倭文",
		"answers": ["しず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "後輪",
		"answers": ["しずわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊歯",
		"answers": ["しだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鞋底魚",
		"answers": ["したびらめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吐綬鶏",
		"answers": ["しちめんちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻腰",
		"answers": ["しっこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹篦",
		"answers": ["しっぺい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹篦返し",
		"answers": ["しっぺがえし",
		"しっぺいがえし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻尾",
		"answers": ["しっぽ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為手",
		"answers": ["して"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為出来す",
		"answers": ["しでかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "埋葬虫",
		"answers": ["しでむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為所",
		"answers": ["しどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "息長鳥",
		"answers": ["しながどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "信濃",
		"answers": ["しなの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "君遷子",
		"answers": ["しなのがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老舗",
		"answers": ["しにせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "東雲",
		"answers": ["しののめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清箱",
		"answers": ["しのはこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "短手",
		"answers": ["しのびで",
		"しのびて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "垣衣",
		"answers": ["しのぶぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "萊草",
		"answers": ["しば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青蝦",
		"answers": ["しばえび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "屢屢",
		"answers": ["しばしば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "底土",
		"answers": ["しはに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "渋団扇",
		"answers": ["しぶうちわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "繁吹",
		"answers": ["しぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "重吹く",
		"answers": ["しぶく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "繁吹く",
		"answers": ["しぶく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地吹雪",
		"answers": ["じふぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "西比利亜",
		"answers": ["しべりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑馬",
		"answers": ["しまうま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蠹魚",
		"answers": ["しみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙魚",
		"answers": ["しみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "衣魚",
		"answers": ["しみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清水",
		"answers": ["しみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "七五三飾",
		"answers": ["しめかざり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "注連飾",
		"answers": ["しめかざり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "搾滓",
		"answers": ["しめかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉蕈",
		"answers": ["しめじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "湿湿",
		"answers": ["じめじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "注連縄",
		"answers": ["しめなわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "七五三縄",
		"answers": ["しめなわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "下総",
		"answers": ["しもうさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仕舞屋",
		"answers": ["しもたや",
		"しもうたや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "下野",
		"answers": ["しもつけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "下野草",
		"answers": ["しもつけそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "細枝",
		"answers": ["しもと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "耆那教",
		"answers": ["じゃいなきょう",
		"じなきょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曲見",
		"answers": ["しゃくみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝦蛄",
		"answers": ["しゃこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青竜蝦",
		"answers": ["しゃこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青竜蝦",
		"answers": ["しゃこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南燭",
		"answers": ["しゃしゃんぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素馨",
		"answers": ["じゃすみん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "耶悉茗",
		"answers": ["じゃすみん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天社蛾",
		"answers": ["しゃちほこが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "襯衣",
		"answers": ["しゃつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吃逆",
		"answers": ["しゃっくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沿階草",
		"answers": ["じゃのひげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三味線",
		"answers": ["しゃみせん",
		"さみせん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "軍鶏",
		"answers": ["しゃも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和人",
		"answers": ["しゃも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洒落",
		"answers": ["しゃれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "爪哇",
		"answers": ["じゃわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三鞭酒",
		"answers": ["しゃんぱん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十姉妹",
		"answers": ["じゅうしまつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "数珠玉",
		"answers": ["じゅずだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寿府",
		"answers": ["じゅねーぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "襦袢",
		"answers": ["じゅばん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "背負子",
		"answers": ["しょいこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兄鷹",
		"answers": ["しょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "少輔",
		"answers": ["しょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "判官",
		"answers": ["じょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生薑",
		"answers": ["しょうが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生姜",
		"answers": ["しょうが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漏斗",
		"answers": ["じょうご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "上手",
		"answers": ["じょうず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如雨露",
		"answers": ["じょうろ",
		"じょろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "如露",
		"answers": ["じょうろ",
		"じょろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女郎蜘蛛",
		"answers": ["じょうろぐも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "絡新婦",
		"answers": ["じょうろぐも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "世帯",
		"answers": ["しょたい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "初中後",
		"answers": ["しょっちゅう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "醢汁",
		"answers": ["しょっつる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "塩汁",
		"answers": ["しょっつる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祥瑞",
		"answers": ["しょんずい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴉葱",
		"answers": ["しらいとそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銀魚",
		"answers": ["しらうお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鱠残魚",
		"answers": ["しらうお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白髪",
		"answers": ["しらが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白髪太郎",
		"answers": ["しらがたろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "新羅",
		"answers": ["しらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白禿瘡",
		"answers": ["しらくも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白癬",
		"answers": ["しらくも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不知不識",
		"answers": ["しらずしらず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不知火",
		"answers": ["しらぬい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素面",
		"answers": ["しらふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白面",
		"answers": ["しらふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "東風菜",
		"answers": ["しらやまぎく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白及",
		"answers": ["しらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "挙尾虫",
		"answers": ["しりあげむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "後方",
		"answers": ["しりえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻繫",
		"answers": ["しりがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尻臀",
		"answers": ["しりこぶた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "後志",
		"answers": ["しりべし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "首級",
		"answers": ["しるし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素魚",
		"answers": ["しろうお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素人",
		"answers": ["しろうと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "越瓜",
		"answers": ["しろうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白灯蛾",
		"answers": ["しろひとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "師走",
		"answers": ["しわす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋酒",
		"answers": ["じん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "星港",
		"answers": ["しんがぽーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "樗蚕",
		"answers": ["しんじゅさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瑞香",
		"answers": ["じんちょうげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沈丁花",
		"answers": ["じんちょうげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "新発意",
		"answers": ["しんぼち",
		"しぼち",
		"しんぼっち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牙婆",
		"answers": ["すあい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "荵冬",
		"answers": ["すいかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忍冬",
		"answers": ["すいかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芋苗",
		"answers": ["ずいき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芋茎",
		"answers": ["ずいき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芋茎祭",
		"answers": ["ずいきまつり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瑞西",
		"answers": ["すいす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螟虫",
		"answers": ["ずいむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瑞典",
		"answers": ["すうぇーでん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘇士",
		"answers": ["すえず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "周防",
		"answers": ["すおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清搔",
		"answers": ["すががき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清し女",
		"answers": ["すがしめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "透百合",
		"answers": ["すかしゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清清しい",
		"answers": ["すがすがしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菅麻",
		"answers": ["すがそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杉天牛",
		"answers": ["すぎかみきり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "問荊",
		"answers": ["すぎな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "接続草",
		"answers": ["すぎな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木菟入",
		"answers": ["ずくにゅう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酸塊",
		"answers": ["すぐり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "次官",
		"answers": ["すけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "助柱",
		"answers": ["すけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "助太刀",
		"answers": ["すけだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "速香",
		"answers": ["すこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘇格蘭",
		"answers": ["すこっとらんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "双六",
		"answers": ["すごろく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寸莎",
		"answers": ["すさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "従者",
		"answers": ["ずさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素戔鳴尊",
		"answers": ["すさのおのみこと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生絹",
		"answers": ["すずし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘿蔔",
		"answers": ["すずしろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清白",
		"answers": ["すずしろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "篠の子",
		"answers": ["すずのこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金鐘児",
		"answers": ["すずむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天蛾",
		"answers": ["すずめが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀の苧桶",
		"answers": ["すずめのおごけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀の小笥",
		"answers": ["すずめのおごけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "看麦娘",
		"answers": ["すずめのてっぽう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡蜂",
		"answers": ["すずめばち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漫事",
		"answers": ["すずろごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "末濃",
		"answers": ["すそご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寸寸",
		"answers": ["ずたずた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魑魅",
		"answers": ["すだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "簾名残",
		"answers": ["すだれなごり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "透波",
		"answers": ["すっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "捨て台詞",
		"answers": ["すてぜりふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "渚鳥",
		"answers": ["すどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "西班牙",
		"answers": ["すぺいん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬歯莧",
		"answers": ["すべりふゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "清汁",
		"answers": ["すましじる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "棠梨",
		"answers": ["ずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酸実",
		"answers": ["ずみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "住処",
		"answers": ["すみか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天皇",
		"answers": ["すめらみこと",
		"すめらぎ",
		"すべらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皇尊",
		"answers": ["すめらみこと",
		"すめらぎ",
		"すべらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "角力",
		"answers": ["すもう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "相撲",
		"answers": ["すもう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掏児",
		"answers": ["すり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掏摸",
		"answers": ["すり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "磨硝子",
		"answers": ["すりがらす",
		"すりガラス"]
	},
	{
		"question": "建蘭",
		"answers": ["するがらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匹如身",
		"answers": ["するすみ",
		"するつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "単己",
		"answers": ["するすみ",
		"するつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鯣烏賊",
		"answers": ["するめいか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素破",
		"answers": ["すわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "楚割",
		"answers": ["すわやり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚条",
		"answers": ["すわやり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飄石",
		"answers": ["ずんばい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石蜐",
		"answers": ["せ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石花",
		"answers": ["せ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海象",
		"answers": ["せいうち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒸籠",
		"answers": ["せいろう",
		"せいろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "錫蘭",
		"answers": ["せいろん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脊黄青鸚哥",
		"answers": ["せきせいいんこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "節季候",
		"answers": ["せきぞろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瞿麦",
		"answers": ["せきちく",
		"なでしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女衒",
		"answers": ["ぜげん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "列卒",
		"answers": ["せこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石漆",
		"answers": ["せしめうるし",
		"いしうるし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "冷笑う",
		"answers": ["せせらわらう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "切匙",
		"answers": ["せっかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狭匙",
		"answers": ["せっかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糴取",
		"answers": ["せどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糶取",
		"answers": ["せどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "錦葵",
		"answers": ["ぜにあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銭占",
		"answers": ["ぜにうら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地銭",
		"answers": ["ぜにごけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "接腰",
		"answers": ["せひえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "摂腰",
		"answers": ["せひえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟬時雨",
		"answers": ["せみしぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "傴僂",
		"answers": ["せむし",
		"くぐせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水芹",
		"answers": ["せり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "台詞",
		"answers": ["せりふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "科白",
		"answers": ["せりふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬼鍼草",
		"answers": ["せんだんぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪隠金亀子",
		"answers": ["せんちこがね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "剪秋羅",
		"answers": ["せんのう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "当薬",
		"answers": ["せんぶり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫萁",
		"answers": ["ぜんまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "撥条",
		"answers": ["ぜんまい",
		"ばね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其奴",
		"answers": ["そいつ",
		"そやつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "象鼻虫",
		"answers": ["ぞうむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素麵",
		"answers": ["そうめん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "索麵",
		"answers": ["そうめん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "諷言",
		"answers": ["そえこと",
		"そえごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曹達水",
		"answers": ["そーだすい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赭土",
		"answers": ["そおに",
		"そほに",
		"そぼに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "続飯",
		"answers": ["そくい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其処",
		"answers": ["そこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其所",
		"answers": ["そこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "若干",
		"answers": ["そこばく",
		"そくばく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "内障",
		"answers": ["そこひ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膂宍",
		"answers": ["そしし",
		"そしじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其方此方",
		"answers": ["そちこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其方",
		"answers": ["そちら",
		"そっち",
		"そなた",
		"そち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "其方退け",
		"answers": ["そっちのけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "外方",
		"answers": ["そっぽ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄蕉",
		"answers": ["そてつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳳尾松",
		"answers": ["そてつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄樹",
		"answers": ["そてつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "背面",
		"answers": ["そとも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕎麦",
		"answers": ["そば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕎麦搔き",
		"answers": ["そばがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀卵斑",
		"answers": ["そばかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀斑",
		"answers": ["そばかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "岨清水",
		"answers": ["そばしみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "側妻",
		"answers": ["そばめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕎麦湯",
		"answers": ["そばゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曾美加久堂",
		"answers": ["そみかくだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘇民書札",
		"answers": ["そみかくだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "抑抑",
		"answers": ["そもそも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "征矢",
		"answers": ["そや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "征箭",
		"answers": ["そや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微風",
		"answers": ["そよかぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "冬青",
		"answers": ["そよご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虚事",
		"answers": ["そらごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虚言",
		"answers": ["そらごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚕豆",
		"answers": ["そらまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "算盤",
		"answers": ["そろばん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十露盤",
		"answers": ["そろばん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弟鷹",
		"answers": ["だい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泰",
		"answers": ["たい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幇間",
		"answers": ["たいこもち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋玉蘭",
		"answers": ["たいさんぼく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "回青橙",
		"answers": ["だいだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臭橙",
		"answers": ["だいだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松明",
		"answers": ["たいまつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金剛石",
		"answers": ["だいやもんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "田人",
		"answers": ["たうど",
		"とうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手弱女",
		"answers": ["たおやめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鷹居",
		"answers": ["たかすえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大芥菜",
		"answers": ["たかな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "高御座",
		"answers": ["たかみくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水爬虫",
		"answers": ["たがめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄刀木",
		"answers": ["たがやさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手抉",
		"answers": ["たくじり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "栲領巾",
		"answers": ["たくひれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "内匠",
		"answers": ["たくみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "内匠寮",
		"answers": ["たくみづかさ",
		"たくみりょう",
		"うちのたくみのつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梟帥",
		"answers": ["たける"]
	},
	{
		"question": "章魚",
		"answers": ["たこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胼胝",
		"answers": ["たこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "担桶",
		"answers": ["たご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紙鳶",
		"answers": ["たこ",
		"いか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "腰輿",
		"answers": ["たごし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "栄蘭",
		"answers": ["たこのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "露兜樹",
		"answers": ["たこのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海燕",
		"answers": ["たこのまくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛸部屋",
		"answers": ["たこべや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檀尻",
		"answers": ["だし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山車",
		"answers": ["だし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "駄洒落",
		"answers": ["だじゃれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "田鶴",
		"answers": ["たず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手繦",
		"answers": ["たすき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄昏",
		"answers": ["たそがれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "誰哉行灯",
		"answers": ["たそやあんどん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "称辞",
		"answers": ["たたえごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三和土",
		"answers": ["たたき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "踏鞴",
		"answers": ["たたら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹈鞴",
		"answers": ["たたら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太刀",
		"answers": ["たち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大刀",
		"answers": ["たち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜀葵",
		"answers": ["たちあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "帯魚",
		"answers": ["たちうお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太刀魚",
		"answers": ["たちうお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太刀打ち",
		"answers": ["たちうち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "立人",
		"answers": ["たちうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太刀風",
		"answers": ["たちかぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "帯刀",
		"answers": ["たちはき",
		"たてわき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "抱瓶",
		"answers": ["だちびん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "方便",
		"answers": ["たつき",
		"たずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "活計",
		"answers": ["たつき",
		"たずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裁衣",
		"answers": ["たっつけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裁着",
		"answers": ["たっつけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海馬",
		"answers": ["たつのおとしご",
		"とど",
		"あしか",
		"せいうち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹瓮",
		"answers": ["たっぺ",
		"たつべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "殺陣",
		"answers": ["たて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊達",
		"answers": ["だて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "経糸",
		"answers": ["たていと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "立女形",
		"answers": ["たておやま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伊達巻",
		"answers": ["だてまき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仮令",
		"answers": ["たとい",
		"たとえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "縦令",
		"answers": ["たとい",
		"たとえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "畳紙",
		"answers": ["たとうがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "帖紙",
		"answers": ["たとうがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "田荘",
		"answers": ["たどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "靉靆く",
		"answers": ["たなびく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水豆児",
		"answers": ["たぬきも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "憑子",
		"answers": ["たのもし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "煙草",
		"answers": ["たばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "足袋",
		"answers": ["たび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "単皮",
		"answers": ["たび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鎮魂",
		"answers": ["たましずめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉章",
		"answers": ["たまずさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "偶偶",
		"answers": ["たまたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葱頭",
		"answers": ["たまねぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "適間",
		"answers": ["たまひま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吉丁虫",
		"answers": ["たまむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉響",
		"answers": ["たまゆら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "彩絵",
		"answers": ["だみえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "訛声",
		"answers": ["だみごえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頑癬",
		"answers": ["たむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "躊躇う",
		"answers": ["ためらう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "容易い",
		"answers": ["たやすい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太夫",
		"answers": ["たゆう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大夫",
		"answers": ["たゆう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大口魚",
		"answers": ["たら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "達便喇嘛",
		"answers": ["だらいらま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "溜込",
		"answers": ["たらしこみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "垂領",
		"answers": ["たりくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "達磨",
		"answers": ["だるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "誰某",
		"answers": ["たれがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "束子",
		"answers": ["たわし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "楽車",
		"answers": ["だんじり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "単寧",
		"answers": ["たんにん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "段梯子",
		"answers": ["だんばしご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "駄袋",
		"answers": ["だんぶくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒲公英",
		"answers": ["たんぽぽ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "暗争",
		"answers": ["だんまり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "暗闘",
		"answers": ["だんまり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾酪",
		"answers": ["ちーず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白茅",
		"answers": ["ちがや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主税",
		"answers": ["ちから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狼尾草",
		"answers": ["ちからしば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扛秤",
		"answers": ["ちきり",
		"ちぎ",
		"ちぎり",
		"ちぎはかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杠秤",
		"answers": ["ちきり",
		"ちぎ",
		"ちぎり",
		"ちぎはかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "断雲",
		"answers": ["ちぎれぐも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "萵苣",
		"answers": ["ちしゃ",
		"ちさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松楊",
		"answers": ["ちしゃのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天青地白",
		"answers": ["ちちこぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斉斉佮爾",
		"answers": ["ちちはる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅渟鯛",
		"answers": ["ちぬだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅生",
		"answers": ["ちふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乳脹",
		"answers": ["ちぶくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "窒扶斯",
		"answers": ["ちふす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "西蔵",
		"answers": ["ちべっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "血塗ろ",
		"answers": ["ちみどろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "炒飯",
		"answers": ["ちゃーはん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "卓袱台",
		"answers": ["ちゃぶだい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "矮鶏",
		"answers": ["ちゃぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金粟蘭",
		"answers": ["ちゃらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哨吶",
		"answers": ["ちゃるめら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬱金香",
		"answers": ["ちゅーりっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金魚蝨",
		"answers": ["ちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚蝨",
		"answers": ["ちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丁香",
		"answers": ["ちょうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水甘草",
		"answers": ["ちょうじそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手水",
		"answers": ["ちょうず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手水鉢",
		"answers": ["ちょうずばち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手斧",
		"answers": ["ちょうな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤古里",
		"answers": ["ちょごり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳥渡",
		"answers": ["ちょっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一寸",
		"answers": ["ちょっと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "点点",
		"answers": ["ちょぼちょぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草石蚕",
		"answers": ["ちょろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉環菜",
		"answers": ["ちょろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甘露子",
		"answers": ["ちょろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "著羅絹",
		"answers": ["ちょろけん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丁髷",
		"answers": ["ちょんまげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "智利",
		"answers": ["ちり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "身柱",
		"answers": ["ちりけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天柱",
		"answers": ["ちりけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "塵手水",
		"answers": ["ちりちょうず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "縮緬雑魚",
		"answers": ["ちりめんじゃこ",
		"ちりめんざこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "銚釐",
		"answers": ["ちろり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "成吉思汗",
		"answers": ["ちんぎすはん",
		"じんぎすかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒猩猩",
		"answers": ["ちんぱんじー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "築牆",
		"answers": ["ついがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一日",
		"answers": ["ついたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朔日",
		"answers": ["ついたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "入梅",
		"answers": ["ついり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "月次",
		"answers": ["つきなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鏡",
		"answers": ["つきひがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "月不見月",
		"answers": ["つきみずつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "筑紫",
		"answers": ["つくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土筆",
		"answers": ["つくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "筆頭菜",
		"answers": ["つくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熟熟",
		"answers": ["つくづく",
		"つらつら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寒蟬",
		"answers": ["つくつくぼうし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木菟鳥",
		"answers": ["つくとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仏掌薯",
		"answers": ["つくねいも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹲踞",
		"answers": ["つくばい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "江浦草",
		"answers": ["つくも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九十九",
		"answers": ["つくも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "江浦草",
		"answers": ["つくも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九十九髪",
		"answers": ["つくもがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "作物所",
		"answers": ["つくもどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄楊",
		"answers": ["つげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柘植",
		"answers": ["つげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菜瓜",
		"answers": ["つけうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "対馬",
		"answers": ["つしま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地錦",
		"answers": ["つた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蔦紅葉",
		"answers": ["つたもみじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土通草",
		"answers": ["つちあけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土木通",
		"answers": ["つちあけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山珊瑚",
		"answers": ["つちあけび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土塊",
		"answers": ["つちくれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛇菰",
		"answers": ["つちとりもち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地胆",
		"answers": ["つちはんみょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛍蛆",
		"answers": ["つちぼたる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "惣暗",
		"answers": ["つつくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "美人局",
		"answers": ["つつもたせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葛籠",
		"answers": ["つづら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九十九折",
		"answers": ["つづらおり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "防已",
		"answers": ["つづらふじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伝手",
		"answers": ["つて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄麻",
		"answers": ["つなそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海嘯",
		"answers": ["つなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海石榴市",
		"answers": ["つばいち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山茶",
		"answers": ["つばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海石榴",
		"answers": ["つばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅花",
		"answers": ["つばな",
		"ちばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乙鳥",
		"answers": ["つばめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "委曲",
		"answers": ["つばら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海螺",
		"answers": ["つぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰蝨",
		"answers": ["つぶじらみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飛礫",
		"answers": ["つぶて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鷸子",
		"answers": ["つぶり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菫菜",
		"answers": ["つぼすみれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "爪紅",
		"answers": ["つまぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀鷂",
		"answers": ["つみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雀鷹",
		"answers": ["つみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "摘入",
		"answers": ["つみれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "抓入",
		"answers": ["つみれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紡錘",
		"answers": ["つむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋毛",
		"answers": ["つむじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋風",
		"answers": ["つむじかぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "心算",
		"answers": ["つもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梅雨",
		"answers": ["つゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鴨跖草",
		"answers": ["つゆくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梅雨寒",
		"answers": ["つゆざむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頰杖",
		"answers": ["つらづえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頰貫",
		"answers": ["つらぬき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長吻虻",
		"answers": ["つりあぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何首烏",
		"answers": ["つるどくだみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊乳",
		"answers": ["つるにんじん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "交尾む",
		"answers": ["つるむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遊牝む",
		"answers": ["つるむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落葵",
		"answers": ["つるむらさき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石蕗",
		"answers": ["つわぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "強者",
		"answers": ["つわもの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "悪阻",
		"answers": ["つわり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "通古斯",
		"answers": ["つんぐーす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為体",
		"answers": ["ていたらく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木偶",
		"answers": ["でく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天蚕糸",
		"answers": ["てぐす",
		"てぐすいと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木偶の坊",
		"answers": ["でくのぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "出会す",
		"answers": ["でくわす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "出交す",
		"answers": ["でくわす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梃子",
		"answers": ["てこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "槓杆",
		"answers": ["てこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勾欄",
		"answers": ["てすり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "手練",
		"answers": ["てだれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丁稚",
		"answers": ["でっち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粘葉装",
		"answers": ["でっちょうそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "出頰",
		"answers": ["でづら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草蝦",
		"answers": ["てながえび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頂辺",
		"answers": ["てへん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄鼬",
		"answers": ["てん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石花菜",
		"answers": ["てんぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅娘",
		"answers": ["てんとうむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓢虫",
		"answers": ["てんとうむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "偽瓢虫",
		"answers": ["てんとうむしだまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桃金嬢",
		"answers": ["てんにんか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丁抹",
		"answers": ["でんまーく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弔上げ",
		"answers": ["といあげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何奴",
		"answers": ["どいつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独逸",
		"answers": ["どいつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三角楓",
		"answers": ["とうかえで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "冬瓜",
		"answers": ["とうがん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "王不留行",
		"answers": ["どうかんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "春宮",
		"answers": ["とうぐう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "礬水",
		"answers": ["どうさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "父さん",
		"answers": ["とうさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灯心",
		"answers": ["とうすみ",
		"とうしみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沢漆",
		"answers": ["とうだいぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灯台躑躅",
		"answers": ["どうだんつつじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "満天星",
		"answers": ["どうだんつつじ",
		"はくちょうげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "唐茄子",
		"answers": ["とうなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蕃南瓜",
		"answers": ["とうなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶤鶏",
		"answers": ["とうまる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "専女",
		"answers": ["とうめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉蜀黍",
		"answers": ["とうもろこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遠江",
		"answers": ["とおとうみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "奎宿",
		"answers": ["とかきぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜥蜴",
		"answers": ["とかげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石竜子",
		"answers": ["とかげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝘蜓",
		"answers": ["とかげ",
		"やもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎食",
		"answers": ["とき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "桃花鳥",
		"answers": ["とき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "朱鷺",
		"answers": ["とき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鯨波",
		"answers": ["とき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常盤",
		"answers": ["ときわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常磐",
		"answers": ["ときわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常磐色",
		"answers": ["ときわいろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常磐木",
		"answers": ["ときわぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常磐津",
		"answers": ["ときわず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木賊",
		"answers": ["とくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳥座",
		"answers": ["とぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳥栖",
		"answers": ["とぐら",
		"とす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "時計",
		"answers": ["とけい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何所",
		"answers": ["どこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野老",
		"answers": ["ところ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "心太",
		"answers": ["ところてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓊脂",
		"answers": ["ところてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏冠菜",
		"answers": ["とさかのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏冠海苔",
		"answers": ["とさかのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "年甲斐",
		"answers": ["としがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祈年",
		"answers": ["としごい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祈年祭",
		"answers": ["としごいのまつり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "年次",
		"answers": ["としなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泥鰌",
		"answers": ["どじょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "七葉樹",
		"answers": ["とち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水鼈",
		"answers": ["とちかがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何方",
		"answers": ["どちら",
		"どっち",
		"どなた",
		"いずかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "把手",
		"answers": ["とって"]
	},
	{
		"question": "縕袍",
		"answers": ["どてら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡獱",
		"answers": ["とど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚屋",
		"answers": ["ととや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馴鹿",
		"answers": ["となかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "舎人",
		"answers": ["とねり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秦皮",
		"answers": ["とねりこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宿直",
		"answers": ["とのい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金線蛙",
		"answers": ["とのさまがえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主殿",
		"answers": ["とのもり",
		"とのも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飛螻蛄",
		"answers": ["とびけら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "濁醪",
		"answers": ["どぶろく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "濁酒",
		"answers": ["どぶろく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海洞花",
		"answers": ["とべら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "点火",
		"answers": ["とぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "左見右見",
		"answers": ["とみこうみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "品部",
		"answers": ["ともべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "響動む",
		"answers": ["どよむ",
		"とよむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "響動く",
		"answers": ["どよめく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "草烏頭",
		"answers": ["とりかぶと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "俘虜",
		"answers": ["とりこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土耳古",
		"answers": ["とるこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜翁",
		"answers": ["とるすとい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吐魯蕃",
		"answers": ["とるふぁん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "薯蕷",
		"answers": ["とろろ",
		"やまのいも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄葵",
		"answers": ["とろろあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄蜀葵",
		"answers": ["とろろあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "永久",
		"answers": ["とわ",
		"とこしえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜻蜓",
		"answers": ["とんぼ",
		"やんま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尚侍",
		"answers": ["ないしのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "掌侍",
		"answers": ["ないしのじょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "典侍",
		"answers": ["ないしのすけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泥梨",
		"answers": ["ないり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泥犂",
		"answers": ["ないり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天一神",
		"answers": ["なかがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長道",
		"answers": ["ながじ",
		"ながち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "中務",
		"answers": ["なかつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "中稲",
		"answers": ["なかて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香螺",
		"answers": ["ながにし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "就中",
		"answers": ["なかんずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹柏",
		"answers": ["なぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水葱",
		"answers": ["なぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亡軀",
		"answers": ["なきがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "亡骸",
		"answers": ["なきがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "薙刀",
		"answers": ["なぎなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長刀",
		"answers": ["なぎなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眉尖刀",
		"answers": ["なぎなた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長押",
		"answers": ["なげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仲人",
		"answers": ["なこうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勿来関",
		"answers": ["なこそのせき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "名残",
		"answers": ["なごり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "余波",
		"answers": ["なごり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梨子地",
		"answers": ["なじじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茄子",
		"answers": ["なす",
		"なすび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茄子紺",
		"answers": ["なすこん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何故",
		"answers": ["なぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菜種梅雨",
		"answers": ["なたねづゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刀豆",
		"answers": ["なたまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪崩",
		"answers": ["なだれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花楸樹",
		"answers": ["ななかまど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚子",
		"answers": ["ななこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無名指",
		"answers": ["ななしゆび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹節虫",
		"answers": ["ななふし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何某",
		"answers": ["なにがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "何卒",
		"answers": ["なにとぞ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "難波",
		"answers": ["なにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浪華",
		"answers": ["なにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浪速",
		"answers": ["なにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浪花",
		"answers": ["なにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "奴国",
		"answers": ["なのくに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "名告",
		"answers": ["なのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "続断",
		"answers": ["なべな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山芹菜",
		"answers": ["なべな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "樹懶",
		"answers": ["なまけもの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鼠",
		"answers": ["なまこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生節",
		"answers": ["なまりぶし",
		"なまぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常歩",
		"answers": ["なみあし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無礼",
		"answers": ["なめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白痢",
		"answers": ["なめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛞蝓",
		"answers": ["なめくじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無礼る",
		"answers": ["なめる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弱竹",
		"answers": ["なよたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寧楽",
		"answers": ["なら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "平城",
		"answers": ["なら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "形姿",
		"answers": ["なりかたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "業平竹",
		"answers": ["なりひらだけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生業",
		"answers": ["なりわい",
		"すぎわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄精",
		"answers": ["なるこゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳴子百合",
		"answers": ["なるこゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "可成",
		"answers": ["なるべく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "縄暖簾",
		"answers": ["なわのれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏臼",
		"answers": ["なんきんはぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南京黄櫨",
		"answers": ["なんきんはぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南天燭",
		"answers": ["なんてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野菰",
		"answers": ["なんばんぎせる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南蛮煙管",
		"answers": ["なんばんぎせる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兄さん",
		"answers": ["にいさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "新墾",
		"answers": ["にいばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "新治",
		"answers": ["にいばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦棟樹",
		"answers": ["にがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄瓜菜",
		"answers": ["にがな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦塩",
		"answers": ["にがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦汁",
		"answers": ["にがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和妙",
		"answers": ["にきたえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和栲",
		"answers": ["にきたえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和幣",
		"answers": ["にきて",
		"にぎて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "幣帛",
		"answers": ["にきて",
		"にぎて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和膚",
		"answers": ["にきはだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柔膚",
		"answers": ["にきはだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "面皰",
		"answers": ["にきび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和魂",
		"answers": ["にきみやま",
		"にぎみたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和御魂",
		"answers": ["にきみやま",
		"にぎみたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和草",
		"answers": ["にこくさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和毛",
		"answers": ["にこげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "柔手",
		"answers": ["にこで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和手",
		"answers": ["にこで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仮漆",
		"answers": ["にす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二進も三進も",
		"answers": ["にっちもさっちも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝸螺",
		"answers": ["にな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鮸膠",
		"answers": ["にべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鰾膠",
		"answers": ["にべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "若気る",
		"answers": ["にやける"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紐育",
		"answers": ["にゅーよーく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郁李",
		"answers": ["にわうめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "接骨木",
		"answers": ["にわとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡蘿蔔",
		"answers": ["にんじん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大蒜",
		"answers": ["にんにく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叩頭虫",
		"answers": ["ぬかずきむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叩頭く",
		"answers": ["ぬかずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "泥濘",
		"answers": ["ぬかるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緯糸",
		"answers": ["ぬきいと",
		"よこいと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盗人猛猛しい",
		"answers": ["ぬすっとたけだけしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "渟足柵",
		"answers": ["ぬたりのさく",
		"ぬたりのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓊音",
		"answers": ["ぬなと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏珠",
		"answers": ["ぬばたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野干玉",
		"answers": ["ぬばたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烏玉",
		"answers": ["ぬばたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "射干玉",
		"answers": ["ぬばたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓊戈",
		"answers": ["ぬほこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微温い",
		"answers": ["ぬるい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白膠木",
		"answers": ["ぬるで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微温湯",
		"answers": ["ぬるまゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盗汗",
		"answers": ["ねあせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "姉さん",
		"answers": ["ねえさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寝心地",
		"answers": ["ねごこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螺旋",
		"answers": ["ねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "捩子",
		"answers": ["ねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螺子",
		"answers": ["ねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "捻子",
		"answers": ["ねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜松",
		"answers": ["ねず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼠坊",
		"answers": ["ねずっぽ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女貞",
		"answers": ["ねずみもち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "年星",
		"answers": ["ねそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "年三",
		"answers": ["ねそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "強請る",
		"answers": ["ねだる",
		"ゆする"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菟糸",
		"answers": ["ねなしかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沢蒜",
		"answers": ["ねびる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "合歓",
		"answers": ["ねむ",
		"ねむのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "合歓木",
		"answers": ["ねむのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "直衣",
		"answers": ["のうし",
		"なおし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "凌霄花",
		"answers": ["のうぜんかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "凌霄葉蓮",
		"answers": ["のうぜんはれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仰領",
		"answers": ["のけくび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦菜",
		"answers": ["のげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熨斗",
		"answers": ["のし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熨斗鮑",
		"answers": ["のしあわび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熨斗蚫",
		"answers": ["のしあわび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熨斗目",
		"answers": ["のしめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "覗機関",
		"answers": ["のぞきからくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野幇間",
		"answers": ["のだいこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "前胡",
		"answers": ["のだけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土当帰",
		"answers": ["のだけ",
		"うど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野阜",
		"answers": ["のづかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "濃餠汁",
		"answers": ["のっぺいじる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長閑",
		"answers": ["のどか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山蒜",
		"answers": ["のびる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和尚菜",
		"answers": ["のぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陳者",
		"answers": ["のぶれば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "逆上せる",
		"answers": ["のぼせる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山石榴",
		"answers": ["のぼたん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野面",
		"answers": ["のもせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "生血",
		"answers": ["のり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祝詞",
		"answers": ["のりと",
		"ほぎごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "諾威",
		"answers": ["のるうぇー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "惚気",
		"answers": ["のろけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "烽火",
		"answers": ["のろし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狼煙",
		"answers": ["のろし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海牙",
		"answers": ["はーぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "婆さん",
		"answers": ["ばあさん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灰神楽",
		"answers": ["はいかぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "高襟",
		"answers": ["はいから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "螺尻",
		"answers": ["ばいじり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "売女",
		"answers": ["ばいた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膝甲",
		"answers": ["はいだて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脛楯",
		"answers": ["はいだて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "膝甲",
		"answers": ["はいだて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海地",
		"answers": ["はいち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳳梨",
		"answers": ["ぱいなっぷる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "延根",
		"answers": ["はいね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "偃松",
		"answers": ["はいまつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "南風",
		"answers": ["はえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蠅虎",
		"answers": ["はえとりぐも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蠅取蜘蛛",
		"answers": ["はえとりぐも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "延縄",
		"answers": ["はえなわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "莫迦",
		"answers": ["ばか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "博士",
		"answers": ["はかせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "果敢無い",
		"answers": ["はかない"]
	},
	{
		"question": "果敢無む",
		"answers": ["はかなむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "捗捗しい",
		"answers": ["はかばかしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡枝花",
		"answers": ["はぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡枝子",
		"answers": ["はぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉鈴花",
		"answers": ["はくうんぼく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "博奕",
		"answers": ["ばくち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "博打",
		"answers": ["ばくち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "六月雪",
		"answers": ["はくちょうげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白丁花",
		"answers": ["はくちょうげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白熊",
		"answers": ["はぐま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉蘭",
		"answers": ["はくもれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬喰",
		"answers": ["ばくろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刷子",
		"answers": ["はけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刷毛",
		"answers": ["はけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雁来紅",
		"answers": ["はげいとう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "錦帯花",
		"answers": ["はこねうつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "箱梯子",
		"answers": ["はこばしご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "方舟",
		"answers": ["はこぶね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "繁縷",
		"answers": ["はこべ",
		"はこべら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白楊",
		"answers": ["はこやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稲架",
		"answers": ["はさ",
		"はざ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "迫間",
		"answers": ["はざま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狭間",
		"answers": ["はざま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "迫間",
		"answers": ["はざま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "剪刀",
		"answers": ["はさみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土師",
		"answers": ["はじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麻疹",
		"answers": ["はしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土師器",
		"answers": ["はじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梯子",
		"answers": ["はしご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "敏捷い",
		"answers": ["はしこい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎茄",
		"answers": ["はしりどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "走野老",
		"answers": ["はしりどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬尾毛",
		"answers": ["ばす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勢車",
		"answers": ["はずみぐるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝦虎魚",
		"answers": ["はぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "爆米",
		"answers": ["はぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沙魚",
		"answers": ["はぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄櫨",
		"answers": ["はぜのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二十重",
		"answers": ["はたえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旅籠",
		"answers": ["はたご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "霹靂神",
		"answers": ["はたたがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二十",
		"answers": ["はたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二十歳",
		"answers": ["はたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雷魚",
		"answers": ["はたはた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "燭魚",
		"answers": ["はたはた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑雪",
		"answers": ["はだれゆき",
		"はだらゆき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "淡竹",
		"answers": ["はちく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二十日",
		"answers": ["はつか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "初東雲",
		"answers": ["はつしののめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飛蝗",
		"answers": ["ばった"]
	},
	{
		"question": "青頭菌",
		"answers": ["はつたけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "初手水",
		"answers": ["はつちょうず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "半被",
		"answers": ["はっぴ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巴布",
		"answers": ["ぱっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伴天連",
		"answers": ["ばてれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "破天連",
		"answers": ["ばてれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "服織",
		"answers": ["はとり",
		"はっとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "服部",
		"answers": ["はとり",
		"はっとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "纏頭",
		"answers": ["はな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫荊",
		"answers": ["はなずおう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "知母",
		"answers": ["はなすげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛縻",
		"answers": ["はなづら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甘蕉",
		"answers": ["ばなな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "煙火",
		"answers": ["はなび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巴奈馬",
		"answers": ["ぱなま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花潜",
		"answers": ["はなむぐり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "瓶爾小草",
		"answers": ["はなやすり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰地蕨",
		"answers": ["はなわらび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "埴瓮",
		"answers": ["はにべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "埴生",
		"answers": ["はにゅう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弾機",
		"answers": ["ばね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "発条",
		"answers": ["ばね",
		"ぜんまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羽隠虫",
		"answers": ["はねかくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "隠翅虫",
		"answers": ["はねかくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "行纏",
		"answers": ["はばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脛巾",
		"answers": ["はばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "脛衣",
		"answers": ["はばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼠麴草",
		"answers": ["ははこぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羽撃く",
		"answers": ["はばたく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "披鍼",
		"answers": ["はばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蔓延る",
		"answers": ["はびこる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "飯匙倩",
		"answers": ["はぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葬帷子",
		"answers": ["はぶりかたびら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛇牀",
		"answers": ["はまぜり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浜茄子",
		"answers": ["はまなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玫瑰",
		"answers": ["はまなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浜梨",
		"answers": ["はまなす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄槿",
		"answers": ["はまぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "文珠蘭",
		"answers": ["はまゆう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浜木綿",
		"answers": ["はまゆう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬銜",
		"answers": ["はみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金花虫",
		"answers": ["はむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甲矢",
		"answers": ["はや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "兄矢",
		"answers": ["はや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "早矢",
		"answers": ["はや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "速歩",
		"answers": ["はやあし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "囃子",
		"answers": ["はやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "疾風",
		"answers": ["はやて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "隼人",
		"answers": ["はやと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "隼人瓜",
		"answers": ["はやとうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流行眼",
		"answers": ["はやりめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流行目",
		"answers": ["はやりめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流行る",
		"answers": ["はやる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "駅馬",
		"answers": ["はゆま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "薔薇",
		"answers": ["ばら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "同胞",
		"answers": ["はらから"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大角",
		"answers": ["はらのふえ",
		"はら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜘蛛抱蛋",
		"answers": ["はらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一葉",
		"answers": ["はらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巴里",
		"answers": ["ぱり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "聖林",
		"answers": ["はりうっど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刺楸",
		"answers": ["はりぎり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉤素",
		"answers": ["はりす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "播磨",
		"answers": ["はりま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "墾道",
		"answers": ["はりみち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "針土竜",
		"answers": ["はりもぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巴爾幹",
		"answers": ["ばるかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "波斯菊",
		"answers": ["はるしゃぎく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫参",
		"answers": ["はるとらのお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "春疾風",
		"answers": ["はるはやて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哈爾賓",
		"answers": ["はるびん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "哈爾浜",
		"answers": ["はるびん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "排球",
		"answers": ["ばれーぼーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "布哇",
		"answers": ["はわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麵麭",
		"answers": ["ぱん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "匈牙利",
		"answers": ["はんがりー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洪牙利",
		"answers": ["はんがりー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三白草",
		"answers": ["はんげしょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熊猫",
		"answers": ["ぱんだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漢堡",
		"answers": ["はんぶるく",
		"はんぶるぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目翳",
		"answers": ["ひ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋琴",
		"answers": ["ぴあの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "廂間",
		"answers": ["ひあわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曾祖父",
		"answers": ["ひいじじ",
		"ひおおじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海狸",
		"answers": ["びーばー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曾祖母",
		"answers": ["ひいばば",
		"ひおおば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "枸榾",
		"answers": ["ひいらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杠谷樹",
		"answers": ["ひいらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十大功労",
		"answers": ["ひいらぎなんてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麦酒",
		"answers": ["びーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "射干",
		"answers": ["ひおうぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石松",
		"answers": ["ひかげのかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "落籍す",
		"answers": ["ひかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日雀",
		"answers": ["ひがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石蒜",
		"answers": ["ひがんばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟇蛙",
		"answers": ["ひきがえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟾蜍",
		"answers": ["ひきがえる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "抽斗",
		"answers": ["ひきだし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰行草",
		"answers": ["ひきよもぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "食火鶏",
		"answers": ["ひくいどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緋秧鶏",
		"answers": ["ひくいな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緋水鶏",
		"answers": ["ひくいな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "茅蜩",
		"answers": ["ひぐらし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小舌",
		"answers": ["ひこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "失声",
		"answers": ["ひごえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "平江帯",
		"answers": ["ひごたい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漏蘆",
		"answers": ["ひごたい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "販女",
		"answers": ["ひさぎめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "販婦",
		"answers": ["ひさぎめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "提子",
		"answers": ["ひさげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊栖菜",
		"answers": ["ひじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿角菜",
		"answers": ["ひじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿尾菜",
		"answers": ["ひじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犇犇",
		"answers": ["ひしひし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緊緊",
		"answers": ["ぴしぴし",
		"びしびし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一向",
		"answers": ["ひたすら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "只管",
		"answers": ["ひたすら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "常陸",
		"answers": ["ひたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緋縮緬",
		"answers": ["ひぢりめん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "喫驚",
		"answers": ["びっくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吃驚",
		"answers": ["びっくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "睡蓮",
		"answers": ["ひつじぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "単衣",
		"answers": ["ひとえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一行",
		"answers": ["ひとくだり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "人心地",
		"answers": ["ひとごこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "他人事",
		"answers": ["ひとごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "人状",
		"answers": ["ひとざま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "石韋",
		"answers": ["ひとつば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海盤車",
		"answers": ["ひとで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "為人",
		"answers": ["ひととなり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "人雪崩",
		"answers": ["ひとなだれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "人頽",
		"answers": ["ひとなだれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "囚獄",
		"answers": ["ひとや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一人",
		"answers": ["ひとり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独り相撲",
		"answers": ["ひとりずもう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "独り法師",
		"answers": ["ひとりぼっち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雛芥子",
		"answers": ["ひなげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "美人草",
		"answers": ["ひなげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雛罌粟",
		"answers": ["ひなげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麗春花",
		"answers": ["ひなげし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日向",
		"answers": ["ひなた",
		"ひゅうが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日次",
		"answers": ["ひなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夷守",
		"answers": ["ひなもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老成",
		"answers": ["ひね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陳生姜",
		"answers": ["ひねしょうが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "終日",
		"answers": ["ひねもす",
		"ひもすがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扁柏",
		"answers": ["ひのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "火熨斗",
		"answers": ["ひのし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹根蛇",
		"answers": ["ひばかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "告天子",
		"answers": ["ひばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雲雀",
		"answers": ["ひばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "向日葵",
		"answers": ["ひまわり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "姫莎草",
		"answers": ["ひめくぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤栴檀",
		"answers": ["ひめしゃら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山丹",
		"answers": ["ひめゆり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神籬",
		"answers": ["ひもろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "素見す",
		"answers": ["ひやかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檜柏",
		"answers": ["びゃくしん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檀香",
		"answers": ["びゃくだん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "風信子",
		"answers": ["ひやしんす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "口琴",
		"answers": ["びやぼん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金糸桃",
		"answers": ["びようやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山蘭",
		"answers": ["ひよどりばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "顋門",
		"answers": ["ひよめき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日和",
		"answers": ["ひより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日和見",
		"answers": ["ひよりみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "曹白魚",
		"answers": ["ひら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扁爪",
		"answers": ["ひらづめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葉手",
		"answers": ["ひらで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葉盤",
		"answers": ["ひらで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金字塔",
		"answers": ["ぴらみっど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "扁虫",
		"answers": ["ひらむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "比目魚",
		"answers": ["ひらめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "撞球",
		"answers": ["びりやーど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋花",
		"answers": ["ひるがお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼓子花",
		"answers": ["ひるがお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋花",
		"answers": ["ひるがお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "昼餉",
		"answers": ["ひるげ",
		"ひるけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "緬甸",
		"answers": ["びるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日女",
		"answers": ["ひるめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日霊",
		"answers": ["ひるめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "肩巾",
		"answers": ["ひれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "領巾",
		"answers": ["ひれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "平伏す",
		"answers": ["ひれふす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒲葵",
		"answers": ["びろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天鵞絨",
		"answers": ["びろーど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天鵝絨",
		"answers": ["びろーど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金翅雀",
		"answers": ["ひわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檜皮",
		"answers": ["ひわだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檜皮色",
		"answers": ["ひわだいろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檜皮葺き",
		"answers": ["ひわだぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "備後表",
		"answers": ["びんごおもて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "編木",
		"answers": ["びんざさら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拍板",
		"answers": ["びんざさら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬢除",
		"answers": ["びんそぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬢枇",
		"answers": ["びんそぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "一揃",
		"answers": ["びんぞろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "回回教",
		"answers": ["ふいふいきょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "費府",
		"answers": ["ふぃらでるふぃあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "比律賓",
		"answers": ["ふぃりぴん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "芬蘭",
		"answers": ["ふぃんらんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白花菜",
		"answers": ["ふうちょうそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "醜男",
		"answers": ["ぶおとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "醜女",
		"answers": ["ぶおんな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "腑甲斐無い",
		"answers": ["ふがいない"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不甲斐無い",
		"answers": ["ふがいない"]
	},
	{
		"question": "深傷",
		"answers": ["ふかで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "菜蕗",
		"answers": ["ふき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "款冬",
		"answers": ["ふき",
		"やまぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不器用",
		"answers": ["ぶきっちょ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "河豚",
		"answers": ["ふぐ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "側金盞花",
		"answers": ["ふくじゅそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰囊",
		"answers": ["ふぐり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿茸",
		"answers": ["ふくろづの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頭垢",
		"answers": ["ふけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雲脂",
		"answers": ["ふけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巫山戯る",
		"answers": ["ふざける"]
	},
	{
		"question": "相応しい",
		"answers": ["ふさわしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "五倍子",
		"answers": ["ふし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酔魚草",
		"answers": ["ふじうつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臥所",
		"answers": ["ふしど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "臥処",
		"answers": ["ふしど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘭草",
		"answers": ["ふじばかま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鵲豆",
		"answers": ["ふじまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豊前",
		"answers": ["ぶぜん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "家猪",
		"answers": ["ぶた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二布",
		"answers": ["ふたの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二幅",
		"answers": ["ふたの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二人",
		"answers": ["ふたり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "両人",
		"answers": ["ふたり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "及己",
		"answers": ["ふたりしずか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恭菜",
		"answers": ["ふだんそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "二日",
		"answers": ["ふつか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宿酔",
		"answers": ["ふつかよい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "筆忠実",
		"answers": ["ふでまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葡萄",
		"answers": ["ぶどう",
		"えび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太占",
		"answers": ["ふとまに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "太兆",
		"answers": ["ふとまに"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蒲桃",
		"answers": ["ふともも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山毛欅",
		"answers": ["ぶな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "発船",
		"answers": ["ふなだち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海蛆",
		"answers": ["ふなむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海蘿",
		"answers": ["ふのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "布海苔",
		"answers": ["ふのり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忽必烈",
		"answers": ["ふびらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忽比烈",
		"answers": ["ふびらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吹雪",
		"answers": ["ふぶき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吹雪く",
		"answers": ["ふぶく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乱吹く",
		"answers": ["ふぶく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蟇子",
		"answers": ["ぶゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "武良尻",
		"answers": ["ぶらじる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伯剌西爾",
		"answers": ["ぶらじる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仏蘭西",
		"answers": ["ふらんす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勃牙利",
		"answers": ["ぶるがりあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "古刃",
		"answers": ["ふるみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "普魯西",
		"answers": ["ぷろしあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豊後",
		"answers": ["ぶんご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "犢鼻褌",
		"answers": ["ふんどし",
		"たふさぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貝独楽",
		"answers": ["べいごま",
		"ばいごま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "折板",
		"answers": ["へぎいた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "日置流",
		"answers": ["へきりゅう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竃食い",
		"answers": ["へぐい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牛皮凍",
		"answers": ["へくそかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "女青",
		"answers": ["へくそかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "褌祝",
		"answers": ["へこいわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "舳先",
		"answers": ["へさき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "圧面",
		"answers": ["べしみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒死病",
		"answers": ["ぺすと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巻子",
		"answers": ["へそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "綜麻",
		"answers": ["へそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "綜麻繰",
		"answers": ["へそくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "下手",
		"answers": ["へた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糸瓜",
		"answers": ["へちま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天糸瓜",
		"answers": ["へちま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "反吐",
		"answers": ["へど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "埴猪口",
		"answers": ["へなちょこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "粘土",
		"answers": ["へなつち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅白粉",
		"answers": ["べにおしろい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "威内斯",
		"answers": ["べにす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅藍花",
		"answers": ["べにばな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陰核",
		"answers": ["へのこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "放屁虫",
		"answers": ["へひりむし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "希伯来",
		"answers": ["へぶらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "部屋",
		"answers": ["へや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "遍羅",
		"answers": ["べら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "倍良",
		"answers": ["べら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "可坊",
		"answers": ["べらぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "便乱坊",
		"answers": ["べらぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "秘露",
		"answers": ["ぺるー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "白耳義",
		"answers": ["べるぎー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伯林",
		"answers": ["べるりん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅殻",
		"answers": ["べんがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "番瀝青",
		"answers": ["ぺんき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "景天",
		"answers": ["べんけいそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "反閉",
		"answers": ["へんばい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "伯耆",
		"answers": ["ほうき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "染指草",
		"answers": ["ほうせんか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孑孑",
		"answers": ["ぼうふら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孑孒",
		"answers": ["ぼうふら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竹麦魚",
		"answers": ["ほうぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "釵子股",
		"answers": ["ぼうらん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "頰輔",
		"answers": ["ほおがまち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鬼灯",
		"answers": ["ほおずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酸漿",
		"answers": ["ほおずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "行器",
		"answers": ["ほかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寿歌",
		"answers": ["ほぎうた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神庫",
		"answers": ["ほくら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒子",
		"answers": ["ほくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黶子",
		"answers": ["ほくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒子",
		"answers": ["ほくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄脚梨",
		"answers": ["ぼけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木瓜",
		"answers": ["ぼけ",
		"きゅうり",
		"まるめろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "反故",
		"answers": ["ほご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "反古",
		"answers": ["ほご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "干鰯",
		"answers": ["ほしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾鰯",
		"answers": ["ほしか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乾海鼠",
		"answers": ["ほしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "熟瓜",
		"answers": ["ほぞち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海扇",
		"answers": ["ほたてがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蛍烏賊",
		"answers": ["ほたるいか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山小菜",
		"answers": ["ほたるぶくろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "上枝",
		"answers": ["ほつえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忽布",
		"answers": ["ほっぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "人面竹",
		"answers": ["ほていちく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "塊芋",
		"answers": ["ほど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土芋",
		"answers": ["ほど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "元宝草",
		"answers": ["ほとけのざ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不如帰",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "時鳥",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郭公花",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沓手鳥",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "霍公鳥",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "油点草",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜鵑草",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "子規",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜鵑",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜀魂",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "杜宇",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郭公",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜀魄",
		"answers": ["ほととぎす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "花瑠瑠",
		"answers": ["ほのるる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微笑む",
		"answers": ["ほほえむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "外持",
		"answers": ["ほまち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海鞘",
		"answers": ["ほや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老海鼠",
		"answers": ["ほや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小火",
		"answers": ["ぼや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吹螺",
		"answers": ["ほらがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葡萄牙",
		"answers": ["ぽるとがる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "母衣",
		"answers": ["ほろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "襤褸",
		"answers": ["ぼろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "珠鶏",
		"answers": ["ほろほろちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微酔",
		"answers": ["ほろよい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "凸柑",
		"answers": ["ぽんかん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香港",
		"answers": ["ほんこん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬尾藻",
		"answers": ["ほんだわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神馬藻",
		"answers": ["ほんだわら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "封度",
		"answers": ["ぽんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "封度",
		"answers": ["ぽんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英斤",
		"answers": ["ぽんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "喞筒",
		"answers": ["ぽんぷ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孟買",
		"answers": ["ぼんべい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪洞",
		"answers": ["ぼんぼり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "迷子",
		"answers": ["まいご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "槙皮",
		"answers": ["まいはだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝸牛被",
		"answers": ["まいまいかぶり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英里",
		"answers": ["まいる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "密夫",
		"answers": ["まおとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "密男",
		"answers": ["まおとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "澳門",
		"answers": ["まかお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "侍婢",
		"answers": ["まかたち",
		"まがたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "侍女",
		"answers": ["まかたち",
		"まがたち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "旋網",
		"answers": ["まきあみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目合",
		"answers": ["まぐわい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "甜瓜",
		"answers": ["まくわうり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "正東風",
		"answers": ["まこち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真砂",
		"answers": ["まさご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真風",
		"answers": ["まじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猿子",
		"answers": ["ましこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真面目",
		"answers": ["まじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不味い",
		"answers": ["まずい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "十寸鏡",
		"answers": ["ますかがみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "益益",
		"answers": ["ますます"]
	},
	{
		"question": "正占",
		"answers": ["ますら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "益荒男",
		"answers": ["ますらお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丈夫",
		"answers": ["ますらお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "丈夫",
		"answers": ["ますらお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大夫",
		"answers": ["ますらお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "籬垣",
		"answers": ["ませがき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬塞棒",
		"answers": ["ませぼう",
		"ませんぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "老成る",
		"answers": ["ませる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "又従兄弟",
		"answers": ["またいとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "又従姉妹",
		"answers": ["またいとこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胯座",
		"answers": ["またぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "股座",
		"answers": ["またぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "苦竹",
		"answers": ["まだけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真章魚",
		"answers": ["まだこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木天蓼",
		"answers": ["またたび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "区区",
		"answers": ["まちまち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真っ赤",
		"answers": ["まっか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松毬",
		"answers": ["まつかさ",
		"まつぼっくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "睫毛",
		"answers": ["まつげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "抹額",
		"answers": ["まっこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "末額",
		"answers": ["まっこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真っ青",
		"answers": ["まっさお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "驀地",
		"answers": ["まっしぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "燐寸",
		"answers": ["まっち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松囃子",
		"answers": ["まつばやし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "松陰囊",
		"answers": ["まつぼっくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山蘿蔔",
		"answers": ["まつむしそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬刀貝",
		"answers": ["まてがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬蛤貝",
		"answers": ["まてがい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬刀葉椎",
		"answers": ["まてばしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "団居",
		"answers": ["まどい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "全人",
		"answers": ["まとうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "正面",
		"answers": ["まとも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真面",
		"answers": ["まとも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "微睡む",
		"answers": ["まどろむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "俎板",
		"answers": ["まないた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眼間",
		"answers": ["まなかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目交",
		"answers": ["まなかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目指",
		"answers": ["まなざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眼指",
		"answers": ["まなざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眼差",
		"answers": ["まなざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目差",
		"answers": ["まなざし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "魚味始",
		"answers": ["まなはじめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "学舎",
		"answers": ["まなびや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "真似",
		"answers": ["まね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眉庇",
		"answers": ["まびさし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "射翳",
		"answers": ["まぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚕簿",
		"answers": ["まぶし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "庶妹",
		"answers": ["ままいも",
		"あらめいも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑杖",
		"answers": ["まむしぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忠実",
		"answers": ["まめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "肉刺",
		"answers": ["まめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大豆粕",
		"answers": ["まめかす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "矮鹿",
		"answers": ["まめじか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豆田",
		"answers": ["まめふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "両下",
		"answers": ["まや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎子",
		"answers": ["まる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬克",
		"answers": ["まるく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬来",
		"answers": ["まれー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "客人",
		"answers": ["まろうど",
		"まれびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "満俺",
		"answers": ["まんがん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金縷梅",
		"answers": ["まんさく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "政所",
		"answers": ["まんどころ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玉柏",
		"answers": ["まんねんすぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "翻車魚",
		"answers": ["まんぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御灯明",
		"answers": ["みあかし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御殿",
		"answers": ["みあらか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御舎",
		"answers": ["みあらか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御稜威",
		"answers": ["みいつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木乃伊",
		"answers": ["みいら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水脈",
		"answers": ["みお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "澪標",
		"answers": ["みおつくし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御薪",
		"answers": ["みかまぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御酒",
		"answers": ["みき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神酒",
		"answers": ["みき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "酒司",
		"answers": ["みきのつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "造酒司",
		"answers": ["みきのつかさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御首",
		"answers": ["みぐし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三行半",
		"answers": ["みくだりはん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水分",
		"answers": ["みくまり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黒三稜",
		"answers": ["みくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三稜草",
		"answers": ["みくり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御饌",
		"answers": ["みけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御食",
		"answers": ["みけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神子",
		"answers": ["みこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皇女",
		"answers": ["みこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巫女",
		"answers": ["みこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "皇子",
		"answers": ["みこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "神輿",
		"answers": ["みこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥撒",
		"answers": ["みさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雎鳩",
		"answers": ["みさご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "身動ぎ",
		"answers": ["みじろぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水蚤",
		"answers": ["みじんこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "針眼",
		"answers": ["みず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "針孔",
		"answers": ["みず",
		"めど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮薔",
		"answers": ["みずあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雨久花",
		"answers": ["みずあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鐙靼",
		"answers": ["みずお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "灯台木",
		"answers": ["みずき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稚子",
		"answers": ["みずこ",
		"みずご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水翻",
		"answers": ["みずこぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼓豆虫",
		"answers": ["みずすまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼓虫",
		"answers": ["みずすまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "不見転",
		"answers": ["みずてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "消梨",
		"answers": ["みずなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水準",
		"answers": ["みずはかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金線草",
		"answers": ["みずひき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御統",
		"answers": ["みすまる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "角髪",
		"answers": ["みずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "角子",
		"answers": ["みずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳩尾",
		"answers": ["みぞおち",
		"みずおち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "晦日",
		"answers": ["みそか",
		"つごもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巧婦鳥",
		"answers": ["みそさざい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "溝三歳",
		"answers": ["みそさざい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "巧婦鳥",
		"answers": ["みそさざい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鷦鷯",
		"answers": ["みそさざい",
		"ささぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "千屈菜",
		"answers": ["みそはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "千屈菜",
		"answers": ["みそはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "祓萩",
		"answers": ["みそはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "溝萩",
		"answers": ["みそはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "屯田",
		"answers": ["みた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恩頼",
		"answers": ["みたまのふゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "恩賚",
		"answers": ["みたまのふゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御手洗",
		"answers": ["みたらし",
		"みたらい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三人",
		"answers": ["みたり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "陸奥",
		"answers": ["みちのく",
		"むつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "睡菜",
		"answers": ["みつがしわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野蜀葵",
		"answers": ["みつば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "省沽油",
		"answers": ["みつばうつぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄瑞香",
		"answers": ["みつまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三椏",
		"answers": ["みつまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "嬰児",
		"answers": ["みどりご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "見惚れる",
		"answers": ["みとれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "見蕩れる",
		"answers": ["みとれる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孤児",
		"answers": ["みなしご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水派",
		"answers": ["みなまた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御哭",
		"answers": ["みね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "刀背打ち",
		"answers": ["みねうち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三布布団",
		"answers": ["みのぶとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "三幅布団",
		"answers": ["みのぶとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御佩刀",
		"answers": ["みはかし",
		"みはかせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "壬生菜",
		"answers": ["みぶな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "任那",
		"answers": ["みまな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚯蚓",
		"answers": ["みみず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "角鴟",
		"answers": ["みみずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木菟",
		"answers": ["みみずく",
		"ずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "完骨",
		"answers": ["みみせせ",
		"せせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "屯倉",
		"answers": ["みやけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "官家",
		"answers": ["みやけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "屯家",
		"answers": ["みやけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土産",
		"answers": ["みやげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "御幸",
		"answers": ["みゆき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "行幸",
		"answers": ["みゆき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "船首",
		"answers": ["みよし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水押",
		"answers": ["みよし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "未蘭",
		"answers": ["みらの"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海松",
		"answers": ["みる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海松布",
		"answers": ["みるめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "嫡妻",
		"answers": ["むかいめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "正妃",
		"answers": ["むかいめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "零余子",
		"answers": ["むかご",
		"ぬかご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蝍蛆",
		"answers": ["むかで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜈蚣",
		"answers": ["むかで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百足",
		"answers": ["むかで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "行縢",
		"answers": ["むかばき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麦薯蕷",
		"answers": ["むぎとろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "麦索",
		"answers": ["むぎなわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尨犬",
		"answers": ["むくいぬ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尨毛",
		"answers": ["むくげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木槿",
		"answers": ["むくげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "樸樹",
		"answers": ["むくのき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮腫",
		"answers": ["むくみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浮腫む",
		"answers": ["むくむ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "起破風",
		"answers": ["むくりはふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "無患子",
		"answers": ["むくろじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼯鼠",
		"answers": ["むささび",
		"ももんが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虫唾",
		"answers": ["むしず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "齲歯",
		"answers": ["むしば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "息子",
		"answers": ["むすこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "産霊神",
		"answers": ["むすびのかみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "睦月",
		"answers": ["むつき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胸座",
		"answers": ["むなぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "郁子",
		"answers": ["むべ",
		"うべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野木瓜",
		"answers": ["むべ",
		"うべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑気",
		"answers": ["むらき",
		"むらぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "漁夫",
		"answers": ["むらぎみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斑濃",
		"answers": ["むらご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "叢時雨",
		"answers": ["むらしぐれ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海布",
		"answers": ["め"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夫婦",
		"answers": ["めおと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眼旗魚",
		"answers": ["めかじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "妻敵",
		"answers": ["めがたき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眼鏡",
		"answers": ["めがね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和布蕪",
		"answers": ["めかぶら",
		"めかぶ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和布刈",
		"answers": ["めかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "小櫱",
		"answers": ["めぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "墨西哥",
		"answers": ["めきしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "妻子",
		"answers": ["めこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目癈",
		"answers": ["めしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "召人",
		"answers": ["めしゅうど",
		"めしうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "囚人",
		"answers": ["めしゅうど",
		"めしびと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "繡眼児",
		"answers": ["めじろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鍍金",
		"answers": ["めっき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "右手",
		"answers": ["めて"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蓍萩",
		"answers": ["めどはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鉄掃箒",
		"answers": ["めどはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "益母草",
		"answers": ["めはじき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目眩",
		"answers": ["めまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "眩暈",
		"answers": ["めまい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "目紛しい",
		"answers": ["めまぐるしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "減上",
		"answers": ["めりかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乙甲",
		"answers": ["めりかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "米利堅",
		"answers": ["めりけん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "莫大小",
		"answers": ["めりやす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "門得尓",
		"answers": ["めんでる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仮面梟",
		"answers": ["めんふくろう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "摩西",
		"answers": ["もーせ",
		"もーぜ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "莫臥児",
		"answers": ["もーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "痘瘡",
		"answers": ["もがさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎落",
		"answers": ["もがり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎落笛",
		"answers": ["もがりぶえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木捻子",
		"answers": ["もくねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木螺子",
		"answers": ["もくねじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "土竜",
		"answers": ["もぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鼴鼠",
		"answers": ["もぐら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木蘭",
		"answers": ["もくれん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "帽額",
		"answers": ["もこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裳階",
		"answers": ["もこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裳層",
		"answers": ["もこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猛者",
		"answers": ["もさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "綟子",
		"answers": ["もじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百舌",
		"answers": ["もず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海雲",
		"answers": ["もずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水雲",
		"answers": ["もずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海蘊",
		"answers": ["もずく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "莫斯科",
		"answers": ["もすくわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "毛斯綸",
		"answers": ["もすりん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "保合",
		"answers": ["もちあい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糯粟",
		"answers": ["もちあわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "糯米",
		"answers": ["もちごめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "厚皮香",
		"answers": ["もっこく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "盛相",
		"answers": ["もっそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "牴牾",
		"answers": ["もどき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "摩納哥",
		"answers": ["もなこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "武士",
		"answers": ["もののふ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尸者",
		"answers": ["ものまさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅絹",
		"answers": ["もみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅葉",
		"answers": ["もみじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄葉",
		"answers": ["もみじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅蜀葵",
		"answers": ["もみじあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅葉葵",
		"answers": ["もみじあおい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅葉卸し",
		"answers": ["もみじおろし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木綿",
		"answers": ["もめん",
		"ゆう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鳥臓",
		"answers": ["ももき",
		"ももぎ",
		"ももげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百磯城",
		"answers": ["ももしき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "身屋",
		"answers": ["もや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "身舎",
		"answers": ["もや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "催合",
		"answers": ["もやい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "唐土",
		"answers": ["もろこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "唐黍",
		"answers": ["もろこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蜀黍",
		"answers": ["もろこし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "摩洛哥",
		"answers": ["もろっこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "両刃",
		"answers": ["もろは"]
	},
	{
		"question": "諸諸",
		"answers": ["もろもろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紋甲烏賊",
		"answers": ["もんごういか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "孟得士瓜",
		"answers": ["もんてすきゅー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "主水",
		"answers": ["もんど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "翻筋斗",
		"answers": ["もんどり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "門土里留",
		"answers": ["もんとりおーる"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八百長",
		"answers": ["やおちょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八百屋",
		"answers": ["やおや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八百万",
		"answers": ["やおよろず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山羊",
		"answers": ["やぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野羊",
		"answers": ["やぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山羊鬚",
		"answers": ["やぎひげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八色の姓",
		"answers": ["やくさのかばね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "自棄",
		"answers": ["やけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "火傷",
		"answers": ["やけど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "焼処",
		"answers": ["やけど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "焼傷",
		"answers": ["やけど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "水蠆",
		"answers": ["やご",
		"やまめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八尺瓊勾玉",
		"answers": ["やさかにのまがたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八尺瓊曲玉",
		"answers": ["やさかにのまがたま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "香具師",
		"answers": ["やし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "玄孫",
		"answers": ["やしゃご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "馬陸",
		"answers": ["やすで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八十",
		"answers": ["やそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八十路",
		"answers": ["やそじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八握",
		"answers": ["やつか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "戴勝",
		"answers": ["やつがしら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八首鳥",
		"answers": ["やつがしら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "九面芋",
		"answers": ["やつがしら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八角金盤",
		"answers": ["やつで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "金剛纂",
		"answers": ["やつで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄居虫",
		"answers": ["やどかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雇女",
		"answers": ["やとな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雇仲居",
		"answers": ["やとな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄生木",
		"answers": ["やどりぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄生蜂",
		"answers": ["やどりばち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡籙",
		"answers": ["やなぐい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥の明後日",
		"answers": ["やのあさって"]
	},
	{
		"question": "矢作",
		"answers": ["やはぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏眼草",
		"answers": ["やはずそう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豹脚蚊",
		"answers": ["やぶか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紫金牛",
		"answers": ["やぶこうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "藪柑子",
		"answers": ["やぶこうじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "流鏑馬",
		"answers": ["やぶさめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "窃衣",
		"answers": ["やぶじらみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "貫衆",
		"answers": ["やぶそてつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "藪煙草",
		"answers": ["やぶたばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天名精",
		"answers": ["やぶたばこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豪猪",
		"answers": ["やまあらし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山峡",
		"answers": ["やまかい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山楝蛇",
		"answers": ["やまかがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "赤楝蛇",
		"answers": ["やまかがし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山賤",
		"answers": ["やまがつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山雀",
		"answers": ["やまがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山胡椒",
		"answers": ["やまこうばし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山香",
		"answers": ["やまこうばし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "商陸",
		"answers": ["やまごぼう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山背",
		"answers": ["やましろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山翡翠",
		"answers": ["やませみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山魚狗",
		"answers": ["やませみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八岐大蛇",
		"answers": ["やまたのおろち"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山祇",
		"answers": ["やまつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山神",
		"answers": ["やまつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大和",
		"answers": ["やまと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山処",
		"answers": ["やまと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大和歌",
		"answers": ["やまとうた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大和魂",
		"answers": ["やまとだましい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "大和撫子",
		"answers": ["やまとなでしこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山脈",
		"answers": ["やまなみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "冬眠鼠",
		"answers": ["やまね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山鼠",
		"answers": ["やまね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "野山薬",
		"answers": ["やまのいも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四照花",
		"answers": ["やまぼうし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "天蚕",
		"answers": ["やままゆ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "楊梅",
		"answers": ["やまもも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "八方",
		"answers": ["やも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寡男",
		"answers": ["やもお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寡婦",
		"answers": ["やもめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鰥夫",
		"answers": ["やもめ",
		"やもお"]
	},
	{
		"question": "守宮",
		"answers": ["やもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "壁虎",
		"answers": ["やもり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥生土器",
		"answers": ["やよいどき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "槍烏賊",
		"answers": ["やりいか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鎗烏賊",
		"answers": ["やりいか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "敗荷",
		"answers": ["やれはす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山原水鶏",
		"answers": ["やんばるくいな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "指切",
		"answers": ["ゆいきり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木綿鬘",
		"answers": ["ゆうかずら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木綿垂",
		"answers": ["ゆうしで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "木綿四手",
		"answers": ["ゆうしで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "長庚",
		"answers": ["ゆうずつ",
		"ゆうつず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夕星",
		"answers": ["ゆうずつ",
		"ゆうつず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "昨夜",
		"answers": ["ゆうべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "所以",
		"answers": ["ゆえん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浴衣",
		"answers": ["ゆかた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "湯帷子",
		"answers": ["ゆかたびら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "所縁",
		"answers": ["ゆかり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪消",
		"answers": ["ゆきげ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鹿薬",
		"answers": ["ゆきざさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪垂",
		"answers": ["ゆきしずり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪風巻",
		"answers": ["ゆきしまき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪達磨",
		"answers": ["ゆきだるま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "虎耳草",
		"answers": ["ゆきのした"]
	},
	{
		"question": "珍珠花",
		"answers": ["ゆきやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "噴雪花",
		"answers": ["ゆきやなぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "行方",
		"answers": ["ゆくえ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "靫負",
		"answers": ["ゆげい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "梅桃",
		"answers": ["ゆすらうめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "英桃",
		"answers": ["ゆすらうめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山桜桃",
		"answers": ["ゆすらうめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "強請",
		"answers": ["ゆすり",
		"ねだり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "交譲木",
		"answers": ["ゆずりは"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雪打",
		"answers": ["ゆた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "雨打",
		"answers": ["ゆた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎種",
		"answers": ["ゆだね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "猶太",
		"answers": ["ゆだや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "湯女",
		"answers": ["ゆな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎庭",
		"answers": ["ゆにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "斎場",
		"answers": ["ゆにわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "湯熨斗",
		"answers": ["ゆのし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "豆腐皮",
		"answers": ["ゆば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弓弭",
		"answers": ["ゆはず",
		"ゆみはず"]
	},
	{
		"question": "浴槽",
		"answers": ["ゆぶね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "忌忌しい",
		"answers": ["ゆゆしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "百合鷗",
		"answers": ["ゆりかもめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "左手",
		"answers": ["ゆんで"]
	},
	{
		"question": "横笛",
		"answers": ["ようじょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "良候",
		"answers": ["ようそろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宜候",
		"answers": ["ようそろ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "益無し",
		"answers": ["ようなし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沃土",
		"answers": ["よーど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "沃度丁幾",
		"answers": ["よーどちんき"]
	},
	{
		"question": "欧羅巴",
		"answers": ["よーろっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寿詞",
		"answers": ["よごと"]
	},
	{
		"question": "横痃",
		"answers": ["よこね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "葦雀",
		"answers": ["よしきり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄席",
		"answers": ["よせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "余所",
		"answers": ["よそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "他所",
		"answers": ["よそ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "余所見",
		"answers": ["よそみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蚊母鳥",
		"answers": ["よたか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "怪鴟",
		"answers": ["よたか"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弥立つ",
		"answers": ["よだつ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夜業",
		"answers": ["よなべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四布布団",
		"answers": ["よのぶとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四幅布団",
		"answers": ["よのぶとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "約翰",
		"answers": ["よはね"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夜尿",
		"answers": ["よばり"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四葩",
		"answers": ["よひら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄泉",
		"answers": ["よみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "黄泉路",
		"answers": ["よみじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "宿花",
		"answers": ["よみはな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "鶏児草",
		"answers": ["よめな"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四方",
		"answers": ["よも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "終夜",
		"answers": ["よもすがら",
		"よすがら"]
	},
	{
		"question": "四方山",
		"answers": ["よもやま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "憑坐",
		"answers": ["よりまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄坐",
		"answers": ["よりまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "尸童",
		"answers": ["よりまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄人",
		"answers": ["よりゅうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "度度",
		"answers": ["よりより"]
	},
	{
		"question": "寄方",
		"answers": ["よるべ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹣跚縞",
		"answers": ["よろけじま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹌踉ける",
		"answers": ["よろける"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹣跚ける",
		"answers": ["よろける"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弱法師",
		"answers": ["よろぼうし",
		"よろぼし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蹌踉めく",
		"answers": ["よろめく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "夜半",
		"answers": ["よわ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅宇",
		"answers": ["らお",
		"らう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拉薩",
		"answers": ["らさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "洋妾",
		"answers": ["らしゃめん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海猟",
		"answers": ["らっこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "獺虎",
		"answers": ["らっこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海獺",
		"answers": ["らっこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "乱波",
		"answers": ["らっぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅甸",
		"answers": ["らてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "拉丁",
		"answers": ["らてん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羊駝",
		"answers": ["らま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "喇嘛教",
		"answers": ["らまきょう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蘭貢",
		"answers": ["らんぐーん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "栗鼠",
		"answers": ["りす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "里斯本",
		"answers": ["りすぼん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "輪鼓",
		"answers": ["りゅうご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "輪子",
		"answers": ["りゅうご"]
	},
	{
		"question": "僂麻質斯",
		"answers": ["りゅーまち",
		"りうまち",
		"ろいまちす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "凜凜しい",
		"answers": ["りりしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "凛凛しい",
		"answers": ["りりしい"]
	},
	{
		"question": "琳閣倫",
		"answers": ["りんかーん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "竜胆",
		"answers": ["りんどう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "淋巴",
		"answers": ["りんぱ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "淋巴腺",
		"answers": ["りんぱせん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "路加伝",
		"answers": ["るかでん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "呂栄",
		"answers": ["るそん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "坩堝",
		"answers": ["るつぼ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "紅玉",
		"answers": ["るびー"]
	},
	{
		"question": "列寧",
		"answers": ["れーにん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "連玉",
		"answers": ["れだま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "檸檬",
		"answers": ["れもん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "蓮華躑躅",
		"answers": ["れんげつつじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "櫺子",
		"answers": ["れんじ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅馬",
		"answers": ["ろーま"]
	},
	{
		"question": "羅府",
		"answers": ["ろさんぜるす"]
	},
	{
		"question": "露西亜",
		"answers": ["ろしあ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "倫敦",
		"answers": ["ろんどん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "分別",
		"answers": ["わいだめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "弁別",
		"answers": ["わいだめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "公魚",
		"answers": ["わかさぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和布",
		"answers": ["わかめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "和布",
		"answers": ["わかめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "若布",
		"answers": ["わかめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "裙蔕菜",
		"answers": ["わかめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稚海藻",
		"answers": ["わかめ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "没分暁漢",
		"answers": ["わからずや"]
	},
	{
		"question": "狐臭",
		"answers": ["わきが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "腋臭",
		"answers": ["わきが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "胡臭",
		"answers": ["わきが"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吾妹",
		"answers": ["わぎも"]
	},
	{
		"question": "病葉",
		"answers": ["わくらば"]
	},
	{
		"question": "戯奴",
		"answers": ["わけ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "若人",
		"answers": ["わこうど"]
	},
	{
		"question": "童謡",
		"answers": ["わざうた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "謡歌",
		"answers": ["わざうた"]
	},
	{
		"question": "俳優",
		"answers": ["わざおぎ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "山葵",
		"answers": ["わさび"]
	},
	{
		"question": "華府",
		"answers": ["わしんとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "華盛頓",
		"answers": ["わしんとん"]
	},
	{
		"question": "勿忘草",
		"answers": ["わすれなぐさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "早生",
		"answers": ["わせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "早稲",
		"answers": ["わせ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海若",
		"answers": ["わたつみ",
		"わだつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "海神",
		"answers": ["わたつみ",
		"わだつみ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "渡座",
		"answers": ["わたまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "移徙",
		"answers": ["わたまし"]
	},
	{
		"question": "戦慄く",
		"answers": ["わななく"]
	},
	{
		"question": "稚鰤",
		"answers": ["わらさ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "童巫子",
		"answers": ["わらわみこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "童巫女",
		"answers": ["わらわみこ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "理無い",
		"answers": ["わりない"]
	},
	{
		"question": "仙蓼",
		"answers": ["われもこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "地楡",
		"answers": ["われもこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吾木香",
		"answers": ["われもこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "吾亦紅",
		"answers": ["われもこう"]
	},
	{
		"question": "藁蓋",
		"answers": ["わろうだ"]
	},
	{
		"question": "円座",
		"answers": ["わろうだ"]
	}]
}
